<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="195">
		<path>./Addams Family Values (USA) (MSU-MD)/Addams Family Values (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Addams Family Values</name>
		<desc>The evil Debbie Jelinksi is harming the Addams family once again... She has kidnapped Baby Pubert, and Uncle Fester is the one who must find him and to bring him back to his loving family. The game is based on the live-action movie of the same name.

Addams Family Values is an action adventure game with slight RPG elements (you gain more hit points while proceeding in the game, can upgrade your equipment and special attacks). You control Fester, by moving him around, fighting regular enemies and bosses, talking to members of Addams household, and occasionally solving puzzles. The combat is pure action,  Zelda-style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Addams Family Values (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Addams Family Values (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Addams Family Values (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>The Addams Family</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles of Rage - Re-Shelled (USA) (MSU-MD)/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles of Rage - Re-Shelled (USA) (MSU-MD) [n].md</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles of Rage - Re-Shelled (USA) (MSU-MD) [n]</name>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="307">
		<path>./Addams Family, The (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Addams Family, The (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>The Addams Family</name>
		<desc>The Addams Family is a platform game based on the characters and settings from the movie (which, in turn, is based on the famous 1960's television series, which in turn is based on Charles Addams cartoon of the same name, which was featured in the magazine, The New Yorker, in the 30's).

The game takes place towards the end of the movie: the Addams Family has been evicted from their home by a court order issued by a backstabbing attorney (there's one for the books), Tully Alford. Even worse, the other Addamses: Morticia, Pugsley, Wednesday, Granny and Lurch have gone missing.

As Gomez, you must tour the Addams mansion in search of your lost family, battling out mysterious monsters and evading traps, and eventually face your nemesis, Tully.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Addams Family, The (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Addams Family, The (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Addams Family, The (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flying Edge</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>The Addams Family</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>5934BD26C6C8F9CCEBC94D24EAC99B8A</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="156">
		<path>./Animaniacs (USA) (MSU-MD)/Animaniacs (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Animaniacs</name>
		<desc>Animaniacs is a side-scrolling action/puzzle game based on the animated TV series of the same name.  The Warner kids, Yakko, Wakko, and Dot have escaped the water tower again and are on a quest to retrieve movie memorabilia from the Warner Bros. studio lot.  

There are 4 stages, and in each stage the Warners must work together to get past obstacles and enemies. Yakko can push or pull boxes, Wakko can use his hammer to smash things, and Dot can blow kisses to charm simple minded foes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Animaniacs (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Animaniacs (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Animaniacs (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Animaniacs</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>1C1E5E9A64947FBABF8AB2F4AD4CA17D</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="456">
		<path>./Art of Fighting (USA) (MSU-MD)/Art of Fighting (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting</name>
		<desc>Yuri Sakazaki has been kidnapped! Her big brother Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia, his best friend, go search for her on the streets of South Town. As they go deeper and deeper they will find clues as to who ordered the kidnapping, the Sakazaki family's relation to the mob, and a person from their past.

This fighting game is a coin-op conversion of the Neo-Geo hit of the same name, and has all characters, stages, and moves featured in the arcade unit. Unlike the original arcade version, players can now play as Mr. Big and the elusive Mr. Karate.

The gameplay differs from most fighting games. In this game, you have a Spirit meter. A Spirit meter is in the game and will decrease as you perform special moves. It can be recharged, but doing so leaves you open to attack. When your health is almost gone, you can perform a secret combination that will unleash a deadly attack on your opponent - provided you have a full Spirit meter.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Art of Fighting (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Art of Fighting (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Art of Fighting (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>8E79486CD306281332B0DDFD7820D011</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="320">
		<path>./Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Chiki Chiki Boys</name>
		<desc>This platform-based adventure was converted from a Capcom arcade game, and set in the land of Alurea. The idyllic life of the Alurean people was shattered when the King is killed by a dragon, and a range of nasties inhabit the lands. Fortunately his twin sons have come to the rescue, and you must take control of one or the other to put the world right.

The boys have differing skills - one is more skilled in sword-fighting (which you are always armed with), the other in magic (available in limited amounts on each level). You collect coins as the game goes on, and spend these in the shop on extra magic, extra lives and enhanced swords.

There are 3 levels on offer - Earth, The Heavens and The Sea, and these can be tackled in any order. The first is straight platform action, the second involves jumping across clouds, and the third sees your characters swim. After those are completed, you must venture into the Monster Castle and finally slay the dragon.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chiki Chiki Boys (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>91838315AD57DC8A4A5FBFEBFD03C9AC</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="45">
		<path>./Daimakaimura ~ Ghouls'n Ghosts (World) (Rev A) (MSU-MD)/Daimakaimura ~ Ghouls'n Ghosts (World) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>Three years have passed since Arthur defeated the Demon King Astaroth and rescued his beloved Princess Prin-Prin (see Ghosts 'N Goblins). A new villain, the Great Demon King Lucifer (Loki in some versions) has become the new leader of Ghoul Realm. While returning from a journey, Arthur sees the Princess' castle and her village under attack by Lucifer's forces. While rushing towards her beloved knight, the Princess is struck by one of Lucifer's laser beams.

Now, Arthur must venture back to the Lucifer's palace and destroy the demon in order to rescue the Princess' soul and bring her back to life! And it won't matter whether he fights in his shining armor or in his underwear alone...the bravest Knight in the land isn't going to be stopped by some monsters! Although the game starts with graveyard and marsh territory familiar from the first game, later levels are set in a tower, a mass of skeletons, and a castle.

Players progress from left to right (from bottom to top in level 3), and have to hack down the aforementioned monsters with a sword. The journey includes ledges, ladders, lava pits and slippery slopes. Different weapons can be collected, by finding suits of armor inside chests. Each of the five stages has its own setting and a final boss.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Daimakaimura ~ Ghouls'n Ghosts (World) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Daimakaimura ~ Ghouls'n Ghosts (World) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Daimakaimura ~ Ghouls'n Ghosts (World) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Ghost'n Goblins</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>800A4F91985EB79A7F9C269F95765D6B</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="474">
		<path>./Daisenpuu ~ Twin Hawk (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Daisenpuu ~ Twin Hawk (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Daisenpuu</name>
		<desc>Twin Hawk is a typical vertical scrolling shooter with a top-down view. Your goal is easy, shoot all the enemies along the way. You only get a standard gun on your plane, and no bombs! Instead of bombs you can call helper planes. These planes make a formation around you and help to shoot all enemies.

Along the way you get the chance to collect power-ups by shooting transport trucks. When these are destroyed they release a power-up. There are 3 types. First is the weapon upgrade, with this you get a wider and more powerful shot. Second, you get more calls for helper planes. And third are extra lives.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Daisenpuu ~ Twin Hawk (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Daisenpuu ~ Twin Hawk (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Daisenpuu ~ Twin Hawk (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>41CF8AF3B10D1D3A9629D2D38D67677B</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="64">
		<path>./Earthworm Jim 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD)/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).md</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim 2</name>
		<desc>An ordinary average earthworm named Jim goes about his normal daily life, cruising around avoiding crows and doing other general worm-like things. Jim is suddenly struck by a very large ultra- high- tech- indestructible- super- space- cyber- suit. Through sheer luck, Jim rests safely in the neck ring of the suit. 

Suddenly, the ultra-high-tech space particles of the suit begin interacting with Jim's soft wormy flesh. A radical light-speed evolution takes place.

Jim soon realizes he is in control of the suit.

Gameplay is similar to the first game, with Jim jumping and running through the levels. There are 5 weapons more than the original game to collect. Characters like Princess Whats-Her-Name and Psy-Crow appear.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playmates Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Earthworm Jim</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>78164C3F73A0B351D22CD30B6D76E2EE</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="426">
		<path>./Elemental Master (USA) (MSU-MD) [MSU-MD Intro-test]/Elemental Master (USA) (MSU-MD) [MSU-MD Intro-test].md</path>
		<name>Elemental Master</name>
		<desc>Elemental Master's gameplay is similar to a top-down space shooter (i.e Raptor &amp; Raiden), but what makes it unique is the fact you play as a human instead of space-ship.

There are different kinds of weapons which you can use. Like other games in the genre you also have tons of strange enemies to destroy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Elemental Master (USA) (MSU-MD) [MSU-MD Intro-test].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Elemental Master (USA) (MSU-MD) [MSU-MD Intro-test].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Elemental Master (USA) (MSU-MD) [MSU-MD Intro-test].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technosoft</developer>
		<publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>71A449E46B36866D51FDFAD246E4DBDA</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="147">
		<path>./Fatal Fury 2 (USA, Korea) (MSU-MD)/Fatal Fury 2 (USA, Korea) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury 2</name>
		<desc>Again, the Lone Wolves return!

Geese Howard may have been defeated, but that doesn't mean all is peaceful. A new opponent, Wolfgang Krauser, has come forth to begin a new Fatal Fury tournament. The Lone Wolves return, with new faces amongst them. Only one can be declared the winner though.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fatal Fury 2 (USA, Korea) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fatal Fury 2 (USA, Korea) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fatal Fury 2 (USA, Korea) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<family>Fatal Fury</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en,kr</lang>
		<region>kr</region>
		<cheevosHash>49B49B6DC6682BCD8AD753346D110BA4</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="462">
		<path>./Fire Shark (USA) (MSU-MD)/Fire Shark (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Fire Shark</name>
		<desc>Fire Shark takes place around a small island in the South Pacific.  It is a continuously-scrolling aerial shooter with a top-down view.  Your World War II era biplane has been modified to shoot lasers and drop powerful bombs. 

There are ten levels in the game in which you will face aerial, aquatic, and ground enemies. They all fire scores of missiles at you in an attempt to knock you from the sky. 

In between levels, your plane will land on a runway for refueling and maintenance.  You will receive bonus points for the number of bombs left in your hold and the number of lightning bolt icons you picked up in the prior level.

There are also many power-ups available in each level.  Slow-moving blimps contain a power-up icon which is revealed after the zeppelin explodes.  Other icons appear when various other enemies or buildings are destroyed.  These power-ups will float around the screen for several seconds. Grabbing them with your plane earns you a weapon upgrade or bonus points.

The standard weapons are the bomb and the Wide Shot.  As power-ups are obtained the number of shots per blast can increase up to 16.  The Wide Shot is a comparatively weak weapon that usually requires multiple hits to take an enemy down.

The Shark Beam is a green laser that fires in a spiral pattern and the strongest weapon of all is the Super Fire.  It will fire continuously while the fire button is held.  Power-ups increase its beam count to 4.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fire Shark (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fire Shark (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fire Shark (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>B17748DD0298526D781EF97757BD6E13</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="324">
		<path>./Flintstones, The (USA) (Taito) (MSU-MD)/Flintstones, The (USA) (Taito) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>The Flintstones</name>
		<desc>This is a platform game based on the famous Flintstones series. The game features many original Flintstones characters, such as Fred, Wilma, Barney, and others. Instead of the usual "save the princess" or "liberate the world" kinds of a plot, "The Flintstones" is mainly based on small quests: Fred has to retrieve a lost item, etc. The large levels are divided into smaller stages. In the end of each level there is a boss battle. The gameplay involves mostly jumping and hitting the enemies on the heads with a club. The health is measured by hearts. During the game Fred will find many useful items, including some that will increase his health level.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Flintstones, The (USA) (Taito) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Flintstones, The (USA) (Taito) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Flintstones, The (USA) (Taito) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19931022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>The Flintstones</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>97BAC5F230E5A81BDE6F7EAF462D3262</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="185">
		<path>./Garfield - Caught in the Act (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Garfield - Caught in the Act (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Garfield : Caught in the Act</name>
		<desc>As lazy cartoon cat Garfield, you're somehow trapped in your TV, that's what happens with too much TV watching. Go and find all remote-control pieces to get out of that box, and check the fridge for a change. The player advances through levels and bonus rounds in his attempt to escape.

Unlike most other platform games of its time, Garfield boasted completely unique art on each of its six levels, both for tile art and character costumes. The levels are inspired by classic movies, but given a Garfield twist, like "Catsablanca" and "The Curse of Cleofartra.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Garfield - Caught in the Act (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Garfield - Caught in the Act (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Garfield - Caught in the Act (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<family>Garfield</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>C896E17B23E14C0F19DDA02C94B4F51D</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="85">
		<path>./Ghostbusters (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Ghostbusters (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Ghostbusters</name>
		<desc>Set after the events of the first movie, Sega's "Ghostbusters" follows the further adventures of Peter, Ray and Egon, as the make their way through six cases in an attempt to piece together a mysterious stone tablet.

Completely different than the Activision title of the same name, the Genesis "Ghostbusters" is a side-scrolling platformer that has the boys in gray running through houses, apartments, a burning house and a high-rise for starters as they battle a myriad of ghosts with their proton blasters.  When the Ghostbusters face off against a boss ghost, they have the ability to trap them the traditional way.

Peter, Ray and Egon, each have different abilities, and can purchase weapon and life upgrades from shops throughout the levels.  Other familiar faces make an appearance, as Slimer offers power-ups, and the Stay-Puft Marshmallow Man returns to settle the score from the movie.  

Solve the mystery of the tablet, and the Ghostbusters have to face off against Jenna, the Goddess of Death and Destruction.  Can the boys save New York one more time?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ghostbusters (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ghostbusters (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghostbusters (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>19CF503A366AFCC676089889C77261D7</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="88">
		<path>./Golden Axe II (World) (MSU-MD)/Golden Axe II (World) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Golden Axe II</name>
		<desc>Not long after the malign reign of the Death Adder has ended, another evil rises. The peace of the land has again been threatened, this time by 'Dark Guld', who was supposed to be imprisoned but apparently isn't. He has instead now got his hands on the Golden Axe, and is using it for his own nasty purposes, and with his minions is causing much chaos.

So once more, Ax-Battler, the fierce barbarian; Tyris-Flare, the fearless Amazon; Gilius Thunderhead, the ferocious dwarf; get up to deal with the oppression, with their might and magic, and recover the Golden Axe.

The hack and slash gameplay, in a medieval fantasy setting, is essentially the same to that of the previous game. Beat up opponents with melee attacks and collect scrolls to launch magical attacks. Moreover,  players can also ride dragons and other beasts and use their attack capabilities to their advantage.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Golden Axe II (World) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Golden Axe II (World) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Golden Axe II (World) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Golden Axe</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>ECF31F0B0602B78616B83DDB40EBDFE9</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="498">
		<path>./Grind Stormer (USA) (MSU-MD)/Grind Stormer (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Grind Stormer</name>
		<desc>This cartridge combines two different localized flavours of the original arcade game. There are two modes, Grind Stormer and V Five. Both offers the same levels and enemies, but have a different approach to how the player can use power-ups.

In this hectic, top-down, vertically-scrolling shooter where the screen is constantly filled with enemies and bullets, players have a constant, unlimited firing rate, enhanced by power-ups that include missiles, target-seeking bullets, shields, additional speed, extra power and bonus points. In Grind Stormer the ship always moves at a fast speed and the player can collect bombs that damage the entire screen and fend off bullets. The other variant V Five takes a Gradius-approach to power-ups, having the player advance through a selection of power-ups shown on the right by collecting tokens. In the first mode power-ups are immediately applied. In the second mode the ship is much slower and the player needs to decide to spend tokens on speed power-ups right away or save them to advance to seeking bullets or additional power.

The game difficulty, amount of lives and continues can be set in the options. After using a continue, the player immediately receives a "Special" power-up granting four wingmen.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grind Stormer (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grind Stormer (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grind Stormer (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>E011B4465466762B1A8E41D9F4BF9C7A</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="196">
		<path>./Hellfire (USA) (MSU-MD)/Hellfire (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Hellfire</name>
		<desc>In the year 2998, humanity has finally reached the stars, and was able to build a prosperous, peaceful society. However, a space matter known as the Black Nebula began to spread, threatening to engulf the galaxies controlled by humans. It turned out that a robotic dictator named Super Mech was behind this occurrence. The Earth sends Captain Lancer, a skillful pilot navigating the powerful CNCS1 aircraft, equipped with the most powerful weapon: the Hellfire...

This is a horizontal space shooter, with the traditional premise of a lone pilot traversing hostile areas and out-manoeuvring and/or destroying quick and numerous enemies. What sets this shooter apart from many other horizontal space shooters is that you choose the direction of your shots at any time between forward, backward, upward+downward and 4-way diagonal. The 4-way diagonal shot is usually the most effective and makes for some interesting gameplay setups, such as stationary guns you can only reach by passing them (while avoiding their shots) and then placing yourself diagonally above them. There is also a bomb to take out multiple enemies. The game has a standard set of pickups: P icons for powering the weapons, S icons for increasing ship speed, B icons for bombs, and score icons.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hellfire (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hellfire (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hellfire (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>97726E268474C5388B3D213145FEBB8D</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="173">
		<path>./Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (MSU-MD) [T-En]/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (MSU-MD) [T-En].md</path>
		<name>Langrisser II</name>
		<desc>"Langrisser II" is a sequel to  Warsong (whose original title is Langrisser). The events of the game take place several years after those described in "Warsong". Gone is the benevolent kingdom of Baltia, and a new power has risen - the Rayguard Empire, led by Emperor Bernhart and his four generals. Recently, Bernhart ordered his army to attack the neighboring countries, obviously searching for something. This "something" might be none else but a legendary evil sword, that makes the one who wields undefeated. It is up to the noble knight Elwin and his friends to stop the Emperor!

"Langrisser II" is a strategy RPG. The army is divided into soldier units and generals, who fight alone and who are usually stronger than a whole unit. Before the scenario begins, you must hire soldiers, buy weapons and items, etc. During the battle, if you come into contact with an enemy unit, an automatic battle sequence occurs. You can also cast healing spells on your units or offensive spells to hurt the enemy.

The major difference between "Langrisser II" and its "remake",  Der Langrisser for SNES, is the absence of branching storyline in Genesis release.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (MSU-MD) [T-En].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Langrisser</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>2307F9B59F0DB27DEFC7EF6A39CC9F1A</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="66">
		<path>./Lemmings (USA) (MSU-MD)/Lemmings (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Lemmings</name>
		<desc>Your task is to rescue the Lemmings across 120 levels of fast-paced puzzling. These creatures simply walk blindly through the world in the hope of reaching safety at the end of the level - unfortunately these levels include steep drops, gaps in the ground, barriers and rivers amongst other hazards.

You are in control not of any individual Lemming, but of a cross-hair, which can be moved over any of the Lemmings. Along the bottom are a selection of functions which can be assigned to a Lemming, including climbing, floating and bashing. You must click to select the appropriate function, then click on the Lemming to activate it. Each level has a different range of skills on offer, a different amount of Lemmings, and a different percentage target in order to progress.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Lemmings (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Lemmings (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lemmings (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Lemmings</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>E5B3DF383FA97CB47C5B06213890E2B7</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="154">
		<path>./Mega Bomberman (USA) (MSU-MD)/Mega Bomberman (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Mega Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Mega Bomberman is a top down strategy game. Control your Bomberman through various levels defeating multiple enemies and plenty of bosses. Each level consist of blocks for exploding and some blocks that don't explode. At times you will need the non-exploding blocks as shelter. The blocks that do explode reveal power-ups and eggs. 

The eggs are the unique twist to this version of Bomberman. When you get a egg, it hatches into a kangaroo. There are multiple kangaroo types, each with their own unique ability. You hop on the back of the kangaroo and utilize it's ability. If you happen to walk into an explosion the kangaroo takes the damage and dies and you continue to live. 

Another unique feature in multiplayer is you can choose your character. Pick one of 9 such as Miner, Tiny, Fat, Cop, Punk(On cover), Lady, Old man, Robot and the original Bomberman.

After selecting your character get ready for battle as you are placed in 1 of the 4 corners of the arena. Now just blow your way through the blocks and attack some opponents. Watch out for their bombs and remember to dodge your own. There are also many arena's to choose from. Each arena has it's own twist such as trap doors, an igloo to hide in, conveyor belts and more.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mega Bomberman (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mega Bomberman (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mega Bomberman (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<family>Bomberman</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>B7B6EF3B201F040A27CD6585831B9A43</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="139">
		<path>./Monster World IV (USA, Europe) (En,Ja) (Virtual Console) (MSU-MD)/Monster World IV (USA, Europe) (En,Ja) (Virtual Console) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Monster World IV</name>
		<desc>This is a sequel to Wonder Boy 5: Monster World 3. You control Asha, the green-haired girlfriend of Shion, the hero of the previous game. One day, Asha was standing on a cliff near her home village, and suddenly heard a mysterious voice calling for help. She decided to leave the village and to embark on an adventure to discover the identity of this mysterious person.

Monster World 4 is essentially a platform game, with slight RPG/adventure elements (puzzles, treasure, equipment, etc.) Asha can jump, run, attack or defend (by pressing the "down" button). She can also use items and equip weapons and armor, talk to people, and open treasure chests. Later in the game, she will also be able to use magic, and a little blue pet animal will assist and help her on her journey. The combat system is very similar to the classical Zelda style. Health and mana points are measured in little hearts, and the more you progress in the game, the more hit points you gain.

The game was released only in Japan. It is sometimes erroneously called "Wonder Boy 6".</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monster World IV (USA, Europe) (En,Ja) (Virtual Console) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Monster World IV (USA, Europe) (En,Ja) (Virtual Console) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monster World IV (USA, Europe) (En,Ja) (Virtual Console) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Wonder Boy</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>A6F2F7299DBE4E61E5D081CE9C1CD76D</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="12">
		<path>./Mortal Kombat (World) (Rev 1) (MSU-MD)/Mortal Kombat (World) (Rev 1) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>Five Hundred years ago, an ancient and well respected Shaolin fighting tournament, held every 50 years, was corrupted by an evil and elderly sorcerer by the name of Shang Tsung.  Shang was accompanied by Prince Goro, a warrior of the Shokan race (a four armed half-human/half-dragon). Knowing that if ten tournaments in a row were won by the Outworld champion, the Earth Realm would be conquered by evil and fall into darkness, Shang entered Goro in the tournament and had him defeat the great Kung Lao. Goro has been  reigning supreme as the undefeated fighting champion for five hundred years now. As the last tournament required draws near, Raiden, Thunder God and protector of the Earth Realm, enacts a plan to tip the scales in the humans favor, Seven fighters step into the arena on Shang Tsung's mysterious island: Shaolin warrior Liu Kang, Special Forces operative Sonya Blade, the mercenary thug Kano, fame-seeking actor Johnny Cage, the ice wielding Lin Kuei warrior Sub-Zero and his undead adversary Scorpion, and Raiden himself.

Mortal Kombat is a side-scrolling 1 on 1 fighting game. Fighting is set as one on one kombat, allowing each player to perform a variety of punches, kicks, and special moves in order to defeat their opponent.  When the opponent faces their second round loss, the winner can perform a finishing move called a "Fatality" on the loser.  The Fatality is a move unique to each fighter that graphically kills the loser in a blood-soaked finale.

Mortal Kombat began its life as a 2-player arcade title. It is notable for its use of digitized actors to represent the game's fighters, as well as its use of copious amounts of blood during gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat (World) (Rev 1) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat (World) (Rev 1) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat (World) (Rev 1) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Mortal Kombat</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>50A4CF71549DA6E846CE2A015FD815C7</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="33">
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II (World) (MSU-MD)/Mortal Kombat II (World) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>The Mortal Kombat fighters, plus several new ones, return for a tournament held by the evil Shang Tsung of the Outworld. The action is one-on-one as before, and famed for its high level of violence and blood (other than the sanitised Nintendo version). There are 5 difficulty levels and optional credits, as well as the usual two player mode including same character duels.

To win the main tournament, the player must beat each of the other human players, before taking on Shang Tsung, Kintaro and finally Shao Kahn. Players have a range of punches and kicks available, as well as flying kicks, uppercuts, roundhouses, and the special moves, which vary for each player. These include throws, uppercuts, long-distance bullets, bicycle kicks and a teleport feature.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat II (World) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat II (World) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat II (World) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Mortal Kombat</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>D612B2AAFC2ADCA23C73396B8F96D717</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="360061">
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II Unlimited (World) (MSU-MD)/Mortal Kombat II Unlimited (World) (MSU-MD) [n].md</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II Unlimited</name>
		<desc>Mortal Kombat II Unlimited is a full scale hack of the Sega Genesis Mortal Kombat II game, Originally work on the hack ceased with version 07, but in 2011 version 1.0 was released which added many new graphical features. This is Mortal Kombat II, with the following cool added extras:

Added a combo system;
Secret fighters now fully playable;
Bosses now fully playable;
More new sounds;
New stages and music from Mortal Kombat 1;
New moves such as Brutality;
New Game Modes such as Practice and Endurance;
Returned biographies/Endings/Intro/VS-screens from the arcade version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat II Unlimited (World) (MSU-MD) [n].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat II Unlimited (World) (MSU-MD) [n].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat II Unlimited (World) (MSU-MD) [n].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smoke</developer>
		<publisher>Smoke</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<family>Mortal Kombat</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>C388CB002CD0917F05C1F2716B25B265</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="186">
		<path>./MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA) (MSU-MD)/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>MUSHA : Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor</name>
		<desc>Dire51, a supercomputer crafted to control a space colony, goes rogue and sends its attack robots, led by mech Big Asia., to destroy mankind. A team of fighters in giant mechs try to stop it, but all but one, Ellinor (Terri in the US version), are killed, leaving Ellinor to save humanity from destruction on his own.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Seismic</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<family>Aleste</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>3234F3C6F731A736FC007240EB2E7F15</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="162">
		<path>./OutRun (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/OutRun (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>OutRun</name>
		<desc>Race across varied terrain in this conversion of one of the most famous arcade racing games. Your Ferrari is at the ready, complete with female passenger, over a series of short tracks.

Gameplay is viewed form just above and behind the car, so you can see it. The roads are full of sharp bends and hazards, contact with which can cause the car to roll and lose you time. On each section of track there is a fork in the road, allowing you to choose which direction you go in. You have to complete 5 track sections in total, out of the 15 in the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/OutRun (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/OutRun (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/OutRun (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>OutRun</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>B1BB15D23385038980821090CCC7D80E</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="1155">
		<path>./Pier Solar and the Great Architects (World) (En,Fr,Es) (Unl) (Mode 1 CD)/Pier Solar and the Great Architects (World) (En,Fr,Es) (Unl) (Mode 1 CD).md</path>
		<name>Pier Solar and the Great Architects</name>
		<desc>In celebration of the 20th Anniversary of the SEGA Mega Drive, WaterMelon is proud to release the system's biggest RPG yet! As Hoston's father lies suffering from a seemingly incurable illness, the botanist and his friends Alina and Edessot set out to discover the cure.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pier Solar and the Great Architects (World) (En,Fr,Es) (Unl) (Mode 1 CD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pier Solar and the Great Architects (World) (En,Fr,Es) (Unl) (Mode 1 CD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pier Solar and the Great Architects (World) (En,Fr,Es) (Unl) (Mode 1 CD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20101215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Watermelon</developer>
		<publisher>Watermelon</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,es,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>DAAD74B872A5F1AFC932E40E2D9825DB</cheevosHash>
		<cheevosId>13109</cheevosId>
	</game>
	<game id="243">
		<path>./Puyo Puyo (Japan) (MSU-MD)/Puyo Puyo (Japan) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo</name>
		<desc>This is a falling pieces puzzle, Puyo Puyo originated on the MSX system and was later turned into an arcade hall version. Get four same-colored puyos touching each other to make them disappear. If more puyos of the same color are connected then they will disappear too. This game can be played simultaneously by two players for a competitive gameplay. Hinder your opponent by making multiple puyo combinations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Puyo Puyo (Japan) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Puyo Puyo (Japan) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Puyo Puyo (Japan) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Puyo Puyo</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>91315C8CC8F963F71779A0A8E501E3C7</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="102">
		<path>./Road Rash II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Road Rash II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Road Rash II</name>
		<desc>A motorcycle racing game with an attitude. You race in varying environments for ever increasing sums of money. With that money you can buy faster and better bikes. There are many objects on the road to watch out for, from cars to rocks to signs, if you hit one you'll go flying and loose valuable time. If you crash too often your bike can get wrecked. You can also attack other racers. The default attack is a punch, but some racers have weapons, which you can steal and use 
against them. The police patrol the various courses, so if you're not careful you can get busted. Road Rash II is not just a racing game but also a fighting game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Road Rash II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Road Rash II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Road Rash II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>8BA20DD745AA38C5AF55B29685D9EE2E</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="213">
		<path>./Rock n' Roll Racing (World) (Mode 1 CD)/Rock n' Roll Racing (World) (Mode 1 CD).md</path>
		<name>Rock n' Roll Racing</name>
		<desc>Rock 'n Roll Racing is an arcade combat racing game. Combat plays a heavy role in the game, as each car has a frontal weapon, such as a laser or missile, and a drop weapon, such as spikes or mines. As you complete races, you get more money to upgrade your car.

The soundtrack features "Born to Be Wild," "Bad to the Bone," "The Peter Gunn Theme," "Highway Star" and "Paranoid."</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rock n' Roll Racing (World) (Mode 1 CD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rock n' Roll Racing (World) (Mode 1 CD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rock n' Roll Racing (World) (Mode 1 CD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>CA66D9D23E5494AC4BE98208038AA1C5</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="5">
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Sonic The Hedgehog</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog is the first of many games starring Sega's premier rodent Sonic. It's a side scrolling platform game with a difference: speed. Sonic rushes through levels with incredible speed, allowing him to traverse loops and jumps with ease. The evil Dr. Robotnik has captured many of Sonic's animal friends and trapped them inside robots. Sonic can free his friends by destroying the robots with his spin attack. Meanwhile, Dr. Robotnik is trying to control the all-powerful chaos emeralds and Sonic must grab them before he does in the 3D rotating bonus levels. Sonic's weapon is his spin attack; while jumping, Sonic destroys hostile robots by touch. Throughout the platforming levels Sonic collects numerous rings. If Sonic is hit by an enemy, all the rings he's carrying fall out and scatter around; Sonic can quickly grab the rings back before they disappear. If Sonic is hit while not carrying any rings, he dies. Collecting 100 rings gives Sonic an extra life. There is also an invincibility bonus which temporarily protects Sonic from all attacks. The game is divided into several "zones", each of them containing three levels. At the end of each zone Sonic confronts Dr. Robotnik in a boss fight. Sonic the Hedgehog is a significant game because it gave Sega it's first real mascot, and established the Genesis as the video game system with "attitude."</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>791158A18470594761D9FEA31B794571</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="3">
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World) (MSU-MD)/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Sonic The Hedgehog 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog 2 is a side-scrolling platformer based around speed, and the sequel to Sonic the Hedgehog. Players run through different worlds called "Zones", each with a specific theme. There are two Acts in nearly all of the 10 Zones, and at the end of each Zone's last Act is a machine that Robotnik controls, which you must defeat to progress. Sonic and Tails can collect rings which are scattered throughout all of the levels. When the player collects 100 rings they earn an extra life. The rings also act as protection - if Sonic is hurt when he is carrying rings, they scatter everywhere and he is briefly invincible. If he is hit again when he has no rings, he'll lose a life. If the player reaches a continue point lamppost with 50 or more rings, they'll be able to access the Special Stage. In this stage, you must gather a set amount of rings in a halfpipe-like stage before you reach a checkpoint. Complete all the checkpoints and you'll earn one of the seven Chaos Emeralds. The game also includes the ability to play the game co-op with a friend - at any time, a player can plug in a second controller and take over the AI controlled Tails. Tails has infinite lives and the camera remains focused on Sonic, meaning that Tails will not hinder play. Sonic (and Tails) can now also get speed from a standing start by holding down and repeatedly pressing the jump button for a "Spin Dash". This is useful when stuck near steep slopes or other areas where you need some momentum. The game also features a 2-player versus mode. This mode is a horizontally split-screen race through levels based on three of the zones in the single player game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>607D88748743DB8DD0439E3A5331D7DB</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="57">
		<path>./Street Fighter II' - Remastered Edition (USA) (MSU-MD)/Street Fighter II' - Remastered Edition (USA) (MSU-MD) [n].md</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II' : Special Champion Edition</name>
		<desc>From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Vega's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as M. Bison, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter II' - Remastered Edition (USA) (MSU-MD) [n].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter II' - Remastered Edition (USA) (MSU-MD) [n].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter II' - Remastered Edition (USA) (MSU-MD) [n].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Street Fighter</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>32235C1666910D36661D5A0214657C8B</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="20">
		<path>./Streets of Rage 2 (USA) (MSU-MD)/Streets of Rage 2 (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Streets of Rage 2</name>
		<desc>After Axel Stone, Blaze Fielding and Adam Hunter destroyed the evil Syndicate leader, Mr. X, the city became a peaceful place to live, and each one of them followed their own paths. One year later, after their reunion, Adam's brother Sammy returned from school to find their apartment in a mess, and Adam nowhere to be seen, and after calling his two friends, one of them notices a photo of Adam chained to a wall, next to someone they knew very well - Mr. X, who returned to turn the peaceful city once again into a war zone. Now, Axel, Blaze, Sammy, and Axel's good friend Max, a pro wrestler, must head out to stop Mr. X once again...hopefully for good...

Streets of Rage 2 differs from the previous title in several ways. There are changes in both graphics (characters now are bigger, more detailed and with more animation frames, and scenarios are less grainy) and gameplay (the rocket move was replaced by a special move that doubles in offense and defense along several new moves), along other new features such as life bars (and names) for all enemies and the radically different new characters.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Streets of Rage 2 (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Streets of Rage 2 (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Streets of Rage 2 (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Streets of Rage</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>EBF7EA04AA9FFB40AFD0D14A99FB6D49</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="78">
		<path>./Strider (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Strider (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Strider</name>
		<desc>The year is 2089AD. In Russia, the evil Grand Master Meio has begun his insane plot to take over the universe. A lone figure drops from a stealth glider into Meio's base. He is Hiryu, Super A-Class Strider. His mission is to defeat the Grand Master and put an end to his plotting once and for all.

Converted from the classic arcade game, Strider lets you run, jump, perform acrobatics and climb walls and overhangs. You wield a plasma sword, called a Cypher, through 5 levels fighting robots and guards, with mid- and end-level bosses.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Strider (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Strider (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Strider (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Strider</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>6A73601659B1E7A4E889F0D153D57634</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="81">
		<path>./Sunset Riders (USA) (MSU-MD)/Sunset Riders (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Sunset Riders</name>
		<desc>The Wild West...full of the criminal element. Sir Richard Rose, the most despicable face in the criminal lot, has enough power to control the mining facilities, cattle ranches, and trading communities and turn everything to his favor. With that much power, he could literally buy himself the Wild West and control everything!

The people need help, desperately. And just as things were looking grim, who should ride into town but 4 men who have made a pact: to put down Sir Richard Rose and make the Wild West a free and peaceful place to live.

Steve, Bob, Billy, and Cormano are the Sunset Riders, and they're about to live out the wildest shootout the Wild West has ever seen...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sunset Riders (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sunset Riders (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sunset Riders (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>C217A56E6430858BAAB10CED94924A1C</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="114">
		<path>./Super Hang-On (Europe) (En,Ja) (Rev A) (MSU-MD)/Super Hang-On (Europe) (En,Ja) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Super Hang On</name>
		<desc>This is a conversion of Sega's popular motorcycle racing arcade game.  In this game you race a motorcycle around the world, completing each section of track within a time limit. There are other bikes on the road, but beating this is not important, so they can be thought of as moving obstacles. Each continent is a different difficulty level: Africa is beginner, Asia is junior, the Americas are senior, and Europe is expert.  

This is a very simple and straightforward game, viewed from behind the bike in 2D (so the screen does not tilt with the bike). The right/left controls are steering, and up/down are gear changes. Your cycle is always moving, and your speed strictly depends on the gear you are in, although contact or running off the road slows the bike down.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Hang-On (Europe) (En,Ja) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Hang-On (Europe) (En,Ja) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Hang-On (Europe) (En,Ja) (Rev A) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19891106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Hang-On</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>EF0448E92E091A01E254B87661D480D8</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="263">
		<path>./Super Monaco GP (USA) (En,Ja) (MSU-MD)/Super Monaco GP (USA) (En,Ja) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Super Monaco GP</name>
		<desc>Super Monaco GP is a modified conversion of the arcade game, a first-person perspective racing game. As well as the famous Monaco course, others from around the world have been added, to give the game a longer shelf life. You must complete qualification sessions and the races as fast as possible.

The Genesis version of Super Monaco adds a complete career mode, however.  In the career mode, your goal is to win a season of races. Unfortunately, you start with a relatively slow car.  By challenging other drivers, you can move to a better team and car, and ultimately win the F1 World Title.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Monaco GP (USA) (En,Ja) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Monaco GP (USA) (En,Ja) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Monaco GP (USA) (En,Ja) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>26E26B590865A4AF849E9F46DB0BA9B5</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="39">
		<path>./Super Shinobi, The (Japan) (MSU-MD)/Super Shinobi, The (Japan) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>The Super Shinobi</name>
		<desc>You are Musashi, master ninja. You are a mystic warrior, who sees and know all things. You are deadly! Now you must destroy the vicious army of Neo Zeed, or Naoko, their beautiful prisoner, dies!
Attack with a ninja sword and shurikens! Somersault over fences while hurling deadly knives! Ward off bullets, death stars and junked cars by leaping, twisting and kicking!
Stalk ninjas, musclemen, Kung Fu gangs and armies of machine gunners through 24 treacherous scenes. The Neo Zeed are masters of disguise. But you are Shinobi, a master in the art of stealth. And you have a secret weapon - ninja magic!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Shinobi, The (Japan) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Shinobi, The (Japan) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Shinobi, The (Japan) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19891202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Shinobi</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<cheevosHash>3122110CD572FE82D94030811BDF8303</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="540">
		<path>./Target Earth (USA) (MSU-MD)/Target Earth (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Target Earth</name>
		<desc>Space shooting game set in the future with Earth under attack by robots.

You are the pilot of a mech robot which can either walk on planet surfaces or fly in space.  There are two types of levels in the game.  Surface levels take place on planets or moons and allow the mech to run and jump to the end of the level while fighting enemies, as in a side scrolling game.  Space levels have no gravity and allow the mech to move in any direction.  The mech can be equipped with a large assortment of machine guns, lasers, and grenades.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Target Earth (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Target Earth (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Target Earth (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>DreamWorks</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>A271CAADDF8F1F5B1AB98B45CA03EEAF</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="299">
		<path>./Tatsujin ~ Truxton (World) (MSU-MD)/Tatsujin ~ Truxton (World) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Truxton</name>
		<desc>Truxton is one of the earlier 2D scrolling shoot-em-ups. Originally an arcade game, the Genesis/Megadrive version was the only home port of the game released in the United States of America and Europe (and is fairly rare to find). The game was released as "Tatsujin" on the PC Engine in Japan as well.

The game features the usual vertical scrolling backdrops, multiple rounds/stages, myriads of enemy fighters, BIG guns and power-ups.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tatsujin ~ Truxton (World) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tatsujin ~ Truxton (World) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tatsujin ~ Truxton (World) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>8D6F8BF130131DAFBCD627BF0F94DD20</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="60">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA) (MSU-MD)/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles : The Hyperstone Heist</name>
		<desc>The Turtles' nemesis Shredder has acquired the HyperStone from Dimension X, and is using its powers to shrink down the city buildings. He threatens to take over the world and challenges the Turtles to deny him, and so the turtles head out to beat the guy once more.

A standard Ninja Turtles beat-em-up action game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Hyperstone Heist (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>5CDBC71B6E4FCAF299E3C57FB2A57F01</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="116">
		<path>./Terminator - Remastered Edition, The (USA) (MSU-MD)/Terminator - Remastered Edition, The (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>The Terminator</name>
		<desc>The Terminator licensed game for the Sega consoles was a fairly standard side-scrolling platform game. However, the game's six levels mirror the story-line of The Terminator movie very closely as you take on the role of Kyle Reese and his quest to save Sarah Connor from termination.

Because the game follows the movie so closely, the first mission which involves blowing up the SkyNet computer and escaping through time is one of the hardest and something that most players remember with love/hate.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Terminator - Remastered Edition, The (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Terminator - Remastered Edition, The (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Terminator - Remastered Edition, The (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<family>Terminator</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>FB89FBF700AE7D0261EDC1DF83ECA98A</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="271">
		<path>./ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA) (MSU-MD)/ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron</name>
		<desc>The sequel to ToeJam &amp; Earl starts off where the first game ends. The two funky aliens have finally gathered all their rocket parts and left Earth for their home planet Funkotron. Accidentally, some earthlings manage to cling on to their spaceship and come along to Funkotron with them.

Being responsible for the huge disturbance the humans are causing on their funky planet, the duo set off to clean up the mess.

The earthlings come in all sorts of surprising forms, kids running around, construction workers, tourists, and the regular wierdos. You can choose either character, or have two players play out together, as you hit the earthlings with special jars that suck them in, so they cud be transported back to Earth.

You meet other Funkotron inhabitants and interact with them, things like helping them find stuff or ringing their doorbell and running away! All these people will help you in getting the job done and preventing Funkotron from losing its funky-ness.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/ToeJam &amp; Earl in Panic on Funkotron (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>5CBF6FB181DA30F8F1C21E7D9AD92734</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="101">
		<path>./Toki - Going Ape Spit (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Toki - Going Ape Spit (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Toki : Going Ape Spit</name>
		<desc>The hero of the game is a young jungle-man named Toki. One day the evil wizard Dr. Stark kidnaps his girlfriend Wanda. When Toki tries to save her, he is turned into a monkey! Now Toki has to find Dr. Stark in his palace, to rescue Wanda, and to become a human being again!

It is a platform game with a lot of various levels: jungle, underwater, volcanic caves, on the ice... Toki's only weapons are spitting on the enemies or jumping on them and crashing them. There are many possibilities to upgrade his spitting "weapon";  for example, if he finds an upgrade, he can spit fireballs. 

This game is ported from an older arcade version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toki - Going Ape Spit (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Toki - Going Ape Spit (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toki - Going Ape Spit (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tad Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>1CBBDF60633304E3179A4A4A3EA78E49</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="473">
		<path>./Top Gear 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD)/Top Gear 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).md</path>
		<name>Top Gear 2</name>
		<desc>This third-person racing game resembles Gremlin's earlier Lotus series, in terms of its general look and feel, right down to the text font used in the game. Your task is to race through 16 countries, each of which features four races, with many real-world circuits recreated in incongruous locations (such as the Monza layout in Ayers Rock, and the old Hockenheim in Vancouver). 

These four-race blocks each represent their own mini-championship, in which you race against 19 cars, needing to finish in the top 10 to continue, and with the top 6 scoring points 10-6-4-3-2-1, and the respective amount of money in thousands. This can be spent on various upgrades, ranging from engine to tires (wet and dry) and from shocks (front, side and rear) to gearboxes. The ideal approach is to buy the more expensive versions ASAP, as you get no saving when upgrading. If you win the four-race championship, you get the next password. 

You get a set amount of nitro boost to use during each race, although bonus nitros, money and instant speed-up token appear on many tracks. Hazards such as puddles, barriers and ramps are also frequent.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Top Gear 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Top Gear 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Top Gear 2 (USA) (Mode 1 CD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>2030656E8923FE8C238D03CFDB3C02CF</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="382">
		<path>./Two Crude Dudes (USA) (MSU-MD)/Two Crude Dudes (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Two Crude Dudes</name>
		<desc>After a nuclear explosion, New York needs rebuilding. This has barely started when the 'Big Valley' gang enters and takes full control themselves. The Government sends a pair of heavies known as the Crude Dudes in to clear them out.

As one of these Crude Dudes, you must travel through tough streets and take out Big Valley's people, destroying their vehicles and avoiding the force of their weaponry. Foes include werewolves, skeletons and hunchbacks. Gameplay is essentially Streets of Rage-style beat 'em up driven, with bosses on each level.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Two Crude Dudes (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Two Crude Dudes (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Two Crude Dudes (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>1565F3E3A3F09FB52458194B2A607C6D</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="367">
		<path>./Warsong (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En]/Warsong (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].md</path>
		<name>Warsong</name>
		<desc>Warsong is the only title of a series of famous strategy games, known as Langrisser in Japan, to ever see an official release outside of Japan. It is set in a typical medieval fantasy setting and features traditional turn-based combat. The player controls several generals who can command up to eight different units ranging from ordinary soldiers and archers to more exotic creatures like mermen or lizards.The generals fight alongside their units, however they are much more powerful and are able to use more diverse commands than just moving and attacking, like recovering a small amount of HP or casting spells. Each unit has certain strengths and weaknesses; for example soldiers are good against archers but weak against cavalry etc. Combat is also influenced heavily by terrain types. When two units engage in combat a small animation, similar to those seen in Advance Wars or Fire Emblem, is shown.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Warsong (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Warsong (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Warsong (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>Treco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Langrisser</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>EFF89715B62DCE8B032940B633D824A1</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="29">
		<path>./Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy in Monster World</name>
		<desc>"Monster World was once a peaceful region. Then, the peace was shattered by an invading army of monsters. A young man named Shion vowed to defeat them and make his land peaceful again."

Wonder Boy In Monster World puts you in control of Shion in his quest to save Monster World from the evil hands of BioMeka.  It controls like your standard platform game - run, jump, and kill enemies.  The game is filled with RPG elements such as talking to townsfolk, collecting money to buy items, upgrading your life, and equipping a variety of armor and weapons - staying very close to the "Zelda format".  You can save your game to continue your quest at a later time.

Wonder Boy In Monster World is the third game in the Monster World spin-off series.  In Japan the game is called Wonder Boy 5: Monster World 3.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wonder Boy in Monster World (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Wonder Boy</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>131E597B18C54BC4E8F7C3F2D61D0B1B</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="198">
		<path>./After Burner II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/After Burner II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>After Burner II</name>
		<desc>Similar to its predecessor, the premise of After Burner II is to get on the F-14 Tomcat and fly mission after mission of shooting planes out of the sky. At your disposal is a vulcan cannon (basically a machine gun) and a limited number of missiles. In some versions of the game the guns fire automatically all the time. Sometimes you come across a friendly supply plane and if you dock with it you can replenish your missiles.

The game is viewed from behind the plane with you fighting wave after wave of enemy fighters. But at heart it offers the usual shooter mechanics, meaning you spend most of your time dodging and shooting. You also can speed up and slow down to deal with enemies which appear behind you.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/After Burner II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/After Burner II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/After Burner II (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>After Burner</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>25EFC59BA838991AA133F7F12633F228</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="202">
		<path>./Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy III : Monster Lair</name>
		<desc>Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair is a quite different game to most of the games in the Wonder Boy series. You play a green-haired dude who must attack the invaders that attempt to collect weapons and use them to destroy the land. The game starts out like a simple platform game, but it's just when Wonder Boy enters the skull further on that the game is transformed into a shoot 'em up, so basically the gameplay consists of action and shooter scenes.

In the action scenes, your vitality decreases as you make your way towards the skull, but this can be restored by collecting fruit. A wide variety of weapons can be picked up, and not only does these allow you to use the weapons for a limited amount of time, but they also increase your vitality. 

In the shooter scenes, you ride your pink friend as you make your way through the scene. Here, your vitality remains static unless you are hit by an enemy passing by. As usual, there is a boss waiting for you at the end which you must defeat. Every boss changes color to show how much damage has been done to it. You have to defeat some bosses in two stages.

If your vitality gets low in each scene, you'll lose a life. You can also choose to have Wonder Girl join you, as two players can play the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Wonder Boy</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>F3980B6733B91375295954110168F925</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="22">
		<path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD)/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>This is the first Mickey Mouse game for Sega consoles. In this game the famous Disney character must face the dangers of weird fantasy lands such as an enchanted forest and a toy world. Mickey must rescue his girlfriend Minnie who's been kidnapped by the evil witch Mizrabel.

The game play follows the traditional 2D hop 'n' bop platform style in both 8-bit and 16-bit versions. Apart from the story and the music, which is the same, all the rest (including controls, moves, stages and, obviously, graphics), are totally different.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19901122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump Scrolling</genre>
		<family>Mickey Mouse</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>6DD458070F05016AC9A9A1FF8B14EF63</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="72">
		<path>./Rocket Knight Adventures (USA) (MSU-MD)/Rocket Knight Adventures (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Rocket Knight Adventures</name>
		<desc>Rocket Knight Adventures is the first side-scrolling action game starring Sparkster.  He lives in the kingdom of Zebulos, and is the bravest of all the Rocket Knights.  One day, an army of pigs comes down to invade the kingdom and capture the princess.  It is up to Sparkster to set things right again.

Most of the gameplay in Rocket Knight Adventures involves using Sparkster's rocket pack and sword.  Sparkster has to fight off many bosses and survive many precarious situations.  The levels are interspersed with a variety of elements, like shooting stages, and giant robot combat.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rocket Knight Adventures (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rocket Knight Adventures (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rocket Knight Adventures (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>790B4316D9FB8B0F47F36CBAB6A57688</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="155">
		<path>./Ys III (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En]/Ys III (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].md</path>
		<name>Ys III</name>
		<desc>Adol's long time friend, Dogi wishes to return to his home town of Redmont after hearing about strange disturbances that are happening there.  Always looking for an adventure, Adol joins him and soon finds out the cause of this new evil.

Ys III breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games and allows Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions.  As well as changing the battle system, the game is now side scrolling instead of the previous games top-down view. Adol also now has the ability to jump.  Not new to the series is the use of magical rings which give Adol different powering up abilities such as healing and shielding.  The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ys III (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ys III (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ys III (USA) (MSU-MD) [T-En].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Action RPG</genre>
		<family>Ys</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>711FB5B71D3EA1C556E3364658C4DAEF</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="326">
		<path>./Zero Wing (Europe) (MSU-MD)/Zero Wing (Europe) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Zero Wing</name>
		<desc>Zero Wing is an horizontal shooter game where the player is in control of a ZIG, an escape pod released after its main ship was attacked and destroyed by the evil cyborg CATS, bent on taking over the world.

Like most games in the genre, there are three color-coded weapons: red (scatter), green (homing) and blue (lasers). Each weapon has three levels of power, and to obtain those, similar upgrades must be collected sequentially. However, what makes the game unique is the ability to use a traction beam to trap an enemy and then throw him against his peers, destroying them.

The game (or the European PAL version) is best known for being the origin of the infamous "All Your Base" 2001 Internet meme.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zero Wing (Europe) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Zero Wing (Europe) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zero Wing (Europe) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>Toaplan</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<cheevosHash>0CF8EE57C232690522FFD451828B5E4F</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="28">
		<path>./Golden Axe (World) (MSU-MD)/Golden Axe (World) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Golden Axe</name>
		<desc>Sega's classic arcade beat-'em-up game, Golden Axe puts in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (a warrior, a dwarf or an amazon) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Golden Axe (World) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Golden Axe (World) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Golden Axe (World) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Golden Axe</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
		<cheevosHash>E7A575CFA9FA9843B7807BAD5F1D15EA</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="41">
		<path>./Michael Jackson's Moonwalker (Japan, USA) (MSU-MD)/Michael Jackson's Moonwalker (Japan, USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Michael Jackson's Moonwalker</name>
		<desc>Michael Jackson's Moonwalker is pretty much based on the Michael Jackson movie. Mr. Big has kidnapped the children and has nasty things in store for them, like drugging them and making them slaves. It's up to Michael to use his powers and save his little friends.

Michael Jackson (MJ) can jump, throw magical stars, and dance to counter his opponents as he looks for the hidden children. Stages come in shape of some of MJ's videos like streets and graveyards.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Michael Jackson's Moonwalker (Japan, USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Michael Jackson's Moonwalker (Japan, USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Michael Jackson's Moonwalker (Japan, USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>jp,en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>84BC1F4290C0EF195A29F0F369F9AA3B</cheevosHash>
	</game>
	<game id="40">
		<path>./Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA) (MSU-MD)/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA) (MSU-MD).md</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Bloodlines</name>
		<desc>In the year 1917, evil had threatened to rise up again in Transylvania. A young lady named Elizabeth Bartley, who was tried as a witch and killed centuries before, was planning to resurrect the Prince of Darkness, Count Dracula, once again.

The latest of the Belmont lineage, John Morris, and his friend Eric Lecarde, must now travel across Europe to the Palace of Versailles in France, where Bartley is planning the resurrection. And in their way stands Dracula's strongest followers yet...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA) (MSU-MD).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA) (MSU-MD).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA) (MSU-MD).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Castlevania</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<cheevosHash>5898A042C2B81EFE58559C1174819973</cheevosHash>
	</game>
</gameList>
