<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Army Men - Major Malfunction.iso</path>
		<name>Army Men: Major Malfunction</name>
		<desc>Army Men: Major Malfunction is a game in the Army Men franchise released by Global Star Software in 2006 for Xbox and PlayStation 2 consoles. The name Major Malfunction is derived from R. Lee Ermey's quote in Full Metal Jacket, "What is your major malfunction, numbnuts?".</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Army Men - Major Malfunction.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Army Men - Major Malfunction.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Army Men - Major Malfunction.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20060414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17 Software Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Azurik Rise of Perathia.iso</path>
		<name>Azurik: Rise of Perathia</name>
		<desc>A high-profile, first-party Xbox title that pits you in a battle to bring justice to your land, Perathia. "Azurik: Rise of Perathia" will have a heavy focus on action, jaw-dropping graphics and a unique, element-based combat system.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Azurik Rise of Perathia.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Azurik Rise of Perathia.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Azurik Rise of Perathia.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adrenium Games</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Buffy the Vampire Slayer.iso</path>
		<name>Buffy the Vampire Slayer</name>
		<desc>Buffy Summers makes her console debut in a third-person action game set within the not-so-peaceful town of Sunnydale, CA. As the 17-year-old Chosen One, Buffy must use her heightened strength and agility to defeat vampires, zombies, and other demons attracted to the town's dangerous proximity to a Hellmouth. Based on the UPN television series known for its unusual blend of action, suspense, comedy, and drama, the game takes place around the timeframe of the show's first and second seasons.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Buffy the Vampire Slayer.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Buffy the Vampire Slayer.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Buffy the Vampire Slayer.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20120818T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Collective</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crimson Sea.iso</path>
		<name>Crimson Sea</name>
		<desc>Travel thousands of years into the future to the galaxy Theophilus. As Sho, your job is to solve the mystery of countless murders that have been committed by an invading alien force. Along the way, you'll decimate hordes of alien creatures and liquid-morphing enemies with customized blaster rifles and plasma swords. Summon the power of Neo-Psionics to blast through hordes of alien menaces in a single move. Now, with Crimson Sea's Phantom Sensor System, use sound and touch to discover the hidden enemy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crimson Sea.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crimson Sea.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crimson Sea.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.iso</path>
		<name>Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon</name>
		<desc>Relive the epic story from the film in the game of Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon. By stepping into the roles of each of the main characters--Li Mu Bai, Yu Shu Lien, Jen, and "Dark Cloud" Lo--you can unleash a variety of fighting techniques, weapons, stunts, and moves against brutally gifted enemies. Characters improve in skill throughout the game, learn new moves, and earn bonuses and rewards as they master the art of Wudan-style fighting.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20031209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LightWeight</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Family Guy.iso</path>
		<name>Family Guy</name>
		<desc>Play through three stories that intersect in typical Family Guy fashion. Be Stewie and match wits against his brother and arch-nemesis Bertram as they vie to take over the world. Take control of Peter and fight to stop Mr. Belvedere who he thinks is trying to take over the world. Slip on a collar and down a martini as Brian attempt to escape prison and prove your innocence in a puppy parental case gone awry.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Family Guy.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Guy.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Family Guy.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20061002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goldeneye Rogue Agent.iso</path>
		<name>GoldenEye: Rogue Agent</name>
		<desc>After being fired from MI6 for your ruthless behavior in an MI-6 simulator, you begin to work for Auric Goldfinger doing evil deeds. After the first mission (Which is the simulator) you are assigned a Goldeneye by Francisco Scaramanga who acts as the villain’s version of 'Q'. Your Goldeneye can do four separate things which are to see through cover, toss enemies around, use a shield, and hack into computers. The levels in this FPS are all basic run-and-gun style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Goldeneye Rogue Agent.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Goldeneye Rogue Agent.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Goldeneye Rogue Agent.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20041122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Greg Hastings Tournament Paintball Max'd.iso</path>
		<name>Greg Hastings' Tournament Paintball Max'd</name>
		<desc>Greg Hastings' Tournament Paintball delivers a realistic paintball experience through the integration of more than 21 licensed pro-players, actual tournament fields, top authentic paintball gear, and design input directly from the pros. The game captures the nuances of the sport with fast, strategic teamwork, angles, maneuverability and accuracy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Greg Hastings Tournament Paintball Max'd.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Greg Hastings Tournament Paintball Max'd.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Greg Hastings Tournament Paintball Max'd.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WXP Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kabuki Warriors.iso</path>
		<name>Kabuki Warriors</name>
		<desc>As a fight promoter for a troop of Kabuki warriors trying to travel from Edo to Kyoto, your actor/samurai must possess both strength and style. Along the way you will have to fight other Kabuki troops, garner the crowds favor to receive tips, and trade warriors with your defeated counterparts. You will need a very accomplished group of samurai when you arrive in Kyoto to defeat the city's star troop.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kabuki Warriors.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kabuki Warriors.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kabuki Warriors.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LightWeight</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Under Fire - The Crusaders.iso</path>
		<name>Kingdom Under Fire: The Crusaders</name>
		<desc>Kingdom Under Fire: The Crusaders is a tactical wargame developed by the Korean studio Phantagram for the Xbox. It is the sequel to the 2001 game Kingdom Under Fire: A War of Heroes, and continues its storyline. Kingdom Under Fire: The Crusaders combines third-person action and role-playing elements in its gameplay, which differs from its predecessor.



Its sequel is Kingdom Under Fire: Heroes. Another sequel is to be released in 2015 entitled Kingdom Under Fire II for PC and PlayStation 4.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kingdom Under Fire - The Crusaders.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kingdom Under Fire - The Crusaders.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kingdom Under Fire - The Crusaders.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Phantagram</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RalliSport Challenge.iso</path>
		<name>RalliSport Challenge</name>
		<desc>You want real rally racing? Try strapping yourself in for the four play modes of Rallisport Challenge. Twenty-five licensed vehicles participate in Conventional Rally, RallyCross, Hill Climb and Ice Racing. Tracks are taken from the real world, with matching terrains and environments. Particle and weather effects heighten the realism. Rallisport Challenge's unique AI engine delivers drivers with their own individual personalities and driving habits, and effective graphics and animations bring it all to life.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/RalliSport Challenge.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/RalliSport Challenge.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/RalliSport Challenge.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DiCE</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc.iso</path>
		<name>Rayman 3: Hoodlum Havoc</name>
		<desc>Rayman's universe has fallen into a chaotic world of wicked powers, bizarre characters, and merciless combat. When Globox accidentally swallows the Lord of the Dark Lums, a fanatic army of trigger-happy Hoodlums wreaks total havoc to get their Lord back. Rayman's only chance is to purge the Dark Lum Lord from the manic Globox, scour the lands for new powers, and battle with hordes of Hoodlum soldiers.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030314T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Robotech Battlecry.iso</path>
		<name>Robotech Battlecry [Collector's Edition]</name>
		<desc>Individually Numbered Limited Edition with Game Soundtrack, Lenticular Art, Original Concept Art, Numbered Dog Tag and Exclusive T-Shirt</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Robotech Battlecry.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robotech Battlecry.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robotech Battlecry.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TDK CORE</developer>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Run Like Hell.iso</path>
		<name>RLH: Run Like Hell</name>
		<desc>Run Like Hell (also known as RLH) is a third-person shooter video game designed by Digital Mayhem and released by Interplay for the PlayStation 2 in late 2002 and for Xbox in early 2003.



Run Like Hell is set on a space station in the distant future. It features the voice talents of Lance Henriksen, Thomas F. Wilson, Clancy Brown, Kate Mulgrew, Michael Ironside and Brad Dourif. The game also features the music of Three Days Grace and Breaking Benjamin, including an exclusive music video of their song "Polyamorous".



The later Xbox version includes one new level and several new alien creatures, while several optional player character skins and additional minigames can also be downloaded via Xbox Live or the Xbox Exhibition 3 demo disc.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Run Like Hell.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Run Like Hell.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Run Like Hell.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20020927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ToeJam &amp; Earl III - Mission to Earth.iso</path>
		<name>ToeJam &amp; Earl III: Mission to Earth</name>
		<desc>The alien duo is back in an all-new adventure. In ToeJam &amp; Earl III: Mission to Earth, ToeJam, Big Earl, and their new friend, Latisha, embark on a mission to retrieve the 12 sacred Albums of Funk, stolen by the inhabitantats of Earth. Across expansive environments, you must guide this group toward a showdown with the evil Anti-Funk. You'll collect a wide variety of power-ups, take on dangerous side quests, and double-team the clueless Earthlings in style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/ToeJam &amp; Earl III - Mission to Earth.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ToeJam &amp; Earl III - Mission to Earth.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ToeJam &amp; Earl III - Mission to Earth.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20021023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tork - Prehistoric Punk.iso</path>
		<name>Tork: Prehistoric Punk</name>
		<desc>Not even time can stand in the way of Tork. This cave boy must travel through time to find those responsible for kidnapping his father and destroying his village. Not your ordinary hero, Tork can change into three spirit animals: a yeti, an armadillo, or a flying squirrel. As Tork, you must face dinosaurs, gargoyles, robots, and more as you fight your way from the Stone Age to the Age of Fantastical Machines. Dodge avalanches, volcanoes, and machines in a variety of fantastic environments.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tork - Prehistoric Punk.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tork - Prehistoric Punk.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tork - Prehistoric Punk.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tiwak</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toxic Grind.iso</path>
		<name>Toxic Grind</name>
		<desc>In the year 2097, BMX riding has been outlawed and a twisted reality game show is the showcase for public execution of these fugitives. The maniacal host of the show, Dixon Von Blass, has eliminated all but a handful of these riders and resorted to injecting his contestants with a powerful toxin before the show. Injected with the deadly toxin, you were chosen to compete through famous locations and time periods. The only way to survive is to complete objectives, avoid deadly obstacles, and pull off insane tricks--all the while avoiding Dixon's henchmen.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toxic Grind.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toxic Grind.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Toxic Grind.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20031201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Shift</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtual Pool Tournament Edition.iso</path>
		<name>Virtual Pool: Tournament Edition</name>
		<desc>The leader in video game billiards chalks up for console with Virtual Pool: Tournament Edition. Virtual Pool offers 18 different pool games on tables from chic Monte Carlo to a dirty biker bar. Shoot some stick with the most advanced billiard physics ever experienced as you bank, angle, and English the trickiest shots imaginable. Virtual Pool: Tournament Edition is widely recognized as the most realistic pool simulator ever developed!

Features:



Multiple locations: a suburban garage, dusty biker bar, and a beachside mansion

18 varieties of pool: 8-ball, 9-ball, Snooker, and 1- and 3-Cushion Billiards

Easy to play: as quick as setting up a shot on a real pool table

Authentic gameplay: most accurate table and ball physics ever--balls roll, fly, and bounce off the table

Library of artistic trick shots: or set up your own to become a true shark</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtual Pool Tournament Edition.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtual Pool Tournament Edition.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Virtual Pool Tournament Edition.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20060908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2K Games</developer>
		<publisher>2K</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yu-Gi-Oh - The Dawn of Destiny.iso</path>
		<name>Yu-Gi-Oh! Dawn of Destiny</name>
		<desc>Marking the debut of the Yu-Gi-Oh franchise on the Xbox, Yu-Gi-Oh! The Dawn of Destiny brings the world of the popular trading card game to Xbox owners. The game features over 1,000 of the latest Yu-Gi-Oh! cards and seamlessly integrates the Yu-Gi-Oh! trading card gameplay and rules with beautiful 3D monster battles. The Dawn of Destiny also includes new duel modes such as Link Duel mode and Triple Duel mode, where players' can test their skills against three duelists.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Yu-Gi-Oh - The Dawn of Destiny.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yu-Gi-Oh - The Dawn of Destiny.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yu-Gi-Oh - The Dawn of Destiny.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20040323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BMX XXX.iso</path>
		<name>BMX XXX</name>
		<desc>BMX XXX is a 2002 video game published by Acclaim Entertainment under their AKA Acclaim banner for the Xbox, Nintendo GameCube and PlayStation 2 and developed by Z-Axis. While primarily a BMX-based action sports title, it earned most of its notoriety for containing nudity, foul language and adult humor. The game allows the player to create female characters that are fully topless and view live-action video clips of real life strippers, also with bare breasts. Consequently, BMX XXX was initially denied classification in Australia. In North America, while the game is available uncensored on the GameCube and Xbox, all naked breasts are covered in the PlayStation 2 version. While the adult content garnered a great deal of publicity for the game, it was almost entirely negative, and it was eventually released to dismal reviews and poor sales.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/BMX XXX.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/BMX XXX.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/BMX XXX.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021110T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Racing, Sports</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4.iso</path>
		<name>Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4</name>
		<desc>The hottest revolution and bestselling video game in the music game category delivers its best dance performance yet on the Xbox with Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4. Jam-packed with new features, modes, music and gameplay, ULTRAMIX4 offers incredible content for casual, beginner and advanced dancers. For first time players, Dance Dance Revolution ULTRAMIX4 is the perfect introductory game in the series with new tutorials and super-easy levels to make anyone a dancing machine.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 4.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Bible Game.iso</path>
		<name>The Bible Game</name>
		<desc>A trivia game to test gamers' biblical knowledge, The Bible Game casts players as contestants on a game show with fast-paced, "beat the buzzer" action and a comical off-screen announcer as emcee. 20 mini- and micro-games with 1,500 questions reinforce inspirational Old Testament teachings such as Jonah and the Whale, David and Goliath, The Tower of Babel, and many more. Multiplayer mode for up to 4 players encourages family members of all ages to play together, and provides a fun alternative for family game nights.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Bible Game.jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/The Bible Game.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Bible Game.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Classified - Sentinel Crisis.iso</path>
		<name>Classified: The Sentinel Crisis</name>
		<desc>Assume the role a Black Ops soldier recruited by the US military's experimental Sentinel program. Your only tools are the intelligent Sentinel combat suit and the multifunction OIWC assault rifle, a weapon of unparalleled versatility and power. The military scientist responsible for the Sentinel Technology is missing in the Balkans. You must join forces with the Rebels to expose the enemy and locate your quarry before the Sentinel Technology falls into hostile hands.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Classified - Sentinel Crisis.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Classified - Sentinel Crisis.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Classified - Sentinel Crisis.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT 2 - Battle Nexus.iso</path>
		<name>TMNT 2: Battle Nexus</name>
		<desc>The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles return--this time featuring simultaneous play for up to four players. In both cooperative and head-to-head modes, you and your friends can play as your favorite green heroes: Leonardo, Michelangelo, Donatello, and Raphael. Punch, kick, and duck your way through battles against The Shredder and his evil pack of Foot Ninjas. Each Turtle has distinct characteristics and abilities, and you can combine moves to perform more than 30 different types of attacks.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TMNT 2 - Battle Nexus.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TMNT 2 - Battle Nexus.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TMNT 2 - Battle Nexus.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Amped - Freestyle Snowboarding.iso</path>
		<name>Amped: Freestyle Snowboarding</name>
		<desc>Rip the ultimate line on wide-open, real mountains packed with challenges. Whether you hit the cliffs, grind fallen trees, jib the rainbow tree rail, or take the hidden paths, you decide where and how you go down. While you pull off insane tricks on rails, kickers, and half pipes, remember to pose for roaming photographers and camera crews. With enough exposure, you'll find your face on magazine covers and videos and even become an international media superstar.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Amped - Freestyle Snowboarding.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Amped - Freestyle Snowboarding.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Amped - Freestyle Snowboarding.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20011119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indie Built</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BloodRayne 2.iso</path>
		<name>BloodRayne 2</name>
		<desc>BloodRayne 2 is an action hack and slash video game and the second game in the BloodRayne series. It does not follow on directly from where BloodRayne finished; instead, it takes place 60 and 70 years later[1] in a contemporary 2000s setting.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/BloodRayne 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/BloodRayne 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/BloodRayne 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Terminal Reality, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate.iso</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate</name>
		<desc>Dead or Alive (Japanese: デッドオアアライブ Hepburn: Deddo Oa Araibu?) is a 1996 fighting game by Tecmo and the first entry in Team Ninja's long-running Dead or Alive series. It was released first in arcades, followed by home ports for the Sega Saturn in Japan, and later for the Sony PlayStation in all regions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20041026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evil Dead - A Fistful of Boomstick.iso</path>
		<name>Evil Dead: A Fistful of Boomstick</name>
		<desc>Fully "armed" with his chainsaw, trusty boomstick, and trademark quips, Ash must once again save Dearborn from the unspeakable horrors spawned from The Book of the Dead. After a vortex to the undead is unwittingly opened, deadites swarm through Dearborn, turning humans into zombies. Now, with Dearborn in chaos and citizens begging for help, Ash must hack and slash his way through the streets and figure out how to close the vortex. Ash soon learns that all is not what it seems--those he trusts may be plotting against him, and the history of Dearborn might be irrevocably changed.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Evil Dead - A Fistful of Boomstick.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Evil Dead - A Fistful of Boomstick.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Evil Dead - A Fistful of Boomstick.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030617T000000</releasedate>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Set Radio Future.iso</path>
		<name>JSRF: Jet Set Radio Future</name>
		<desc>The setting is Tokyo, in the year 2024. Featuring unique anime-style graphics and tons of tricks, JSRF: Jet Set Radio Future brings the hippest game ever into a futuristic world. Choose a character, strap on your rocket-powered skates, and immerse yourself in the vast environments. The multiplayer aspects let you work together to reach seemingly unattainable places, create new attacks, and perform astounding stunts. Wherever your adventure takes you, it's all about extreme skating, extreme action, and of course extreme style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Set Radio Future.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jet Set Radio Future.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jet Set Radio Future.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Various</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Simpsons - Road Rage.iso</path>
		<name>The Simpsons: Road Rage</name>
		<desc>Mr. Burns is up to his greedy ways in Simpsons Road Rage, purchasing Springfield's busses and jacking up the fares. Now, Springfield residents must turn their cars into cabs and work the streets. Hopefully, making enough money to buy back the busses before the clock runs out. Choose from over 30 of your favorite Simpsons characters and brave the jam-packed streets of six huge levels, performing big-air and powerslide stunts. Compete for passengers in two-player, split screen action. Go on a road rage, Simpsons-style.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Simpsons - Road Rage.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Simpsons - Road Rage.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Simpsons - Road Rage.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20011201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fox Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Night Caster - Defeat the Darkness (Europe) (En,Fr,De).iso</path>
		<name>Nightcaster</name>
		<desc>Battling against eternal darkness, you are Arran, a young wizard embarking on quest filled with explosive spell combat and adventure. Armed with your magical orb and immense spell collection, you age from a young wizard into an older powerful sorcerer. Defeat your enemies with a revolutionary control system: direct movement with one analog stick and aim with the other. Embrace your destiny; restore light to your homeland.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Night Caster - Defeat the Darkness (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Night Caster - Defeat the Darkness (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Night Caster - Defeat the Darkness (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
		<releasedate>20020121T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15001" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Voodoo Vince (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).iso</path>
		<name>Voodoo Vince</name>
		<desc>No Pain, No Gain!



Vince was just a voodoo doll in a French Quarter shop, but when his maker was kidnapped, he became a vengeful doll on a mission! Using voodoo powers, Vince must kick his own butt to beat his enemies! If he stand under a falling safe, bad guys get flattened! Stick a pitch fork in him, and his enemies are done!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beep Industries</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Voodoo Vince (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Voodoo Vince (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Voodoo Vince (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15491" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zan Kabuki (Japan).iso</path>
		<name>Kabuki Warriors</name>
		<desc>As a fight promoter for a troop of Kabuki warriors trying to travel from Edo to Kyoto, your actor/samurai must possess both strength and style. Along the way you will have to fight other Kabuki troops, garner the crowds favor to receive tips, and trade warriors with your defeated counterparts. You will need a very accomplished group of samurai when you arrive in Kyoto to defeat the city's star troop.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zan Kabuki (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Zan Kabuki (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zan Kabuki (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Light Weight</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14752" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Counterstrike.iso</path>
		<name>Counter-Strike</name>
		<desc>Counter-Strike is a first-person shooter in which players join either the terrorist or counter-terrorist team (or become a spectator). Each team attempts to complete their mission objective and/or eliminate the opposing team. Each round starts with the two teams spawning simultaneously.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Counterstrike.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Counterstrike.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Counterstrike.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20031205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>259</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14642" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dino Crisis 3.iso</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis 3</name>
		<desc>Dino Crisis 3 is the third game in the Dino Crisis series, and this time, it's futuristic.



The year is 2548. The colonist spaceship Ozmandias, which disappeared over 300 years ago, suddenly reappears, with no warning or reason to it's disappearance. Attempting to contact the ship results in nothing. The Interstellar Fleet Commander sends out the Special Operations and Reconnaissance (SOAR) squadron to investigate. Their shuttle is destroyed by a merciless and unknown assailant. Everyone manages to survive, and reach the ship intact. What they encounter is something they never would've thought of.



As Patrick, the leader of SOAR, you are tasked with exploring the ship, putting the pieces together, and rescuing any survivors you can find. The ship you are on, the Ozymandias, is a dynamically changing structure, which enables you to move hallways and re-position doors so that you can access new areas all the time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dino Crisis 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dino Crisis 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dino Crisis 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20031107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14611" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fable - The Lost Chapters.iso</path>
		<name>Fable : The Lost Chapters</name>
		<desc>The Lost Chapters features all the content found in the original Fable, as well as additional new content such as new monsters, weapons, alignment based spells, items, armour, towns, buildings, and expressions, as well as the ability to give children objects. The story receives further augmentation in the form of nine new areas and sixteen additional quests. Characters such as Briar Rose and Scythe, who played only minor roles in the original game, are now given more importance and are included in certain main and side quests. Other character-based augmentations include the voice of the antagonist, Jack of Blades, sounding deeper, harsher and more demonic, and the ability to uncover (and resolve) the murder mystery of Lady Grey's sister.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fable - The Lost Chapters.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fable - The Lost Chapters.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fable - The Lost Chapters.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Lionhead</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14974" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gun Valkyrie (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Gun Valkyrie</name>
		<desc>Gun Valkyrie est un jeu d'action sorti sur Xbox. Choisissez un des deux personnages jouables puis partez à la rescousse des colons de Tir Na Nog, une lointaine planète. Préparez-vous à massacrer de l'insecte alien en pagaille.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gun Valkyrie (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gun Valkyrie (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gun Valkyrie (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14932" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hunter - The Reckoning - Redeemer (USA, Japan).iso</path>
		<name>Hunter : The Reckoning Redeemer</name>
		<desc>Hunter : The Reckoning Redeemer est un jeu d'action sur Xbox. Choisissez un des 5 personnages jouables pour aller affronter les forces du mal. Chacun des personnages a des caractéristiques propres à utiliser dans le combat.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hunter - The Reckoning - Redeemer (USA, Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hunter - The Reckoning - Redeemer (USA, Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hunter - The Reckoning - Redeemer (USA, Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<players>24</players>
	</game>
	<game id="14675" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Midtown Madness 3.iso</path>
		<name>Midtown Madness 3</name>
		<desc>Midtown Madness 3 est un jeu de courses urbaines sorti sur Xbox. Pilotez 30 véhicules différents dans les rues de Washington et Paris. Vous devrez vous frayer un chemin à travers les passants et la circulation dense de ces deux mégalopoles.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Midtown Madness 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Midtown Madness 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Midtown Madness 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Illusions</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15006" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Quantum Redshift (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Quantum Redshift</name>
		<desc>It's 100 years in the future, and hyper-speed racing is a sport watched by millions of spectators around the globe. The competitors are armed to the teeth with a variety of destructive weapons, with the aim of gaining race advantage over the other racers. Furthermore, there are numerous personal rivalries between the drivers, as fierce vendettas are played out on the racetrack. The game features 16 fast and challenging tracks, which are extensive and non-linear. Competitors race over desert sands, mountain snow, great lakes and city streets in a tournament which takes them all over the world. 16 un-lockable characters, each with a unique and fully-customisable craft, blast towards the finish line accompanied by the progressive dance beats of JXL. With emotions running high, the competitors enter the fastest show on earth, very much aware that second-place really is nowhere....</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Quantum Redshift (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Quantum Redshift (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Quantum Redshift (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Curly Monsters</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14696" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Soulcalibur II.iso</path>
		<name>SoulCalibur II</name>
		<desc>SoulCalibur II est un jeu de combat sur Xbox. Mesurez-vous à une pléiade d'adversaires en duels armés dans des décors sublimes et tentez d'aller jusqu'au bout pour détruire l'épée maléfique. 13 personnages sont disponibles, ainsi qu'un personnage bonus propre à chaque console (Heihachi sur PS2, Link sur GC et Spawn sur Xbox). Divers modes de jeu sont disponibles, tels que Combat en équipe, Arcade, Contre la montre, Combat VS et Maître d'armes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Soulcalibur II.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soulcalibur II.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soulcalibur II.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14896" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Whacked! (USA Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Whacked!</name>
		<desc>In Whacked! you are one of seven demented contestants competing on a dangerous game show. Pitted against each other in free-for-all combat, contestants must use power-ups and weapons, such as giant staplers and rubber ducky grenades, to flatten their opponents. The game's various modes have you fighting to collect resources, fending off a horde of man-eating chickens, or exchanging blows in fierce deathmatches. There are more than a dozen levels--including an arctic pipeline, a Christmas tree, and a kitchen sink--for you to conquer.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Whacked! (USA Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Whacked! (USA Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Whacked! (USA Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Presto Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14749" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kingdom Under Fire - Heroes (World) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ko).iso</path>
		<name>Kingdom Under Fire : Heroes</name>
		<desc>Kingdom under Fire : Heroes sur Xbox est la suite de The Crusaders, et se place toujours dans le registre de l'action stratégique. Choisissez l'un des 7 invincibles chefs de guerre et commandez une centaine de soldats, de catapultes et de dragons sur des champs de bataille épiques et sur lesquelles les épées s'entrechoquent et les sortilèges pleuvent.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kingdom Under Fire - Heroes (World) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ko).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Kingdom Under Fire - Heroes (World) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ko).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kingdom Under Fire - Heroes (World) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ko).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blueside Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Phantagram Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<genreid>1280</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15148" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Circus Maximus - Chariot Wars (Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Circus Maximus : Chariot Wars</name>
		<desc>Circus Maximus sur Xbox vous fait participer à de dantesques courses de char dans la Rome Antique où les coups bas sont légion. Vous devrez à la fois gérer votre allure pour ne pas fatiguer vos chevaux ni vous planter dans le décor mais aussi surveiller les autres coureurs qui n'auront de cesse que de vous faire chuter.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Circus Maximus - Chariot Wars (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Circus Maximus - Chariot Wars (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Circus Maximus - Chariot Wars (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20020614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Encore Software</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Fight</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15045" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Conan (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Conan</name>
		<desc>Conan sur Xbox est un jeu d'action vous permettant d'incarner le célèbre héros fantaisiste dans ses aventures. Le jeu vous propose de suivre le héros dans 5 régions différentes d'Hyborée, des steppes glacées de Cimérie aux jungles humides de Dafar. De nombreux lieux servent ainsi de décor dans ce jeu qui ne fait pas dans la dentelle.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Conan (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Conan (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Conan (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TDK</developer>
		<publisher>Cauldron</publisher>
		<players>7</players>
	</game>
	<game id="14778" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MechAssault 2 - Lone Wolf (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Mechassault 2 : Lone Wolf</name>
		<desc>Mechassault 2 : Lone Wolf sur Xbox est un jeu d'action dans lequel vous dirigez un personnage installé dans une combinaison de combat. Luttez contre vos ennemis, eux aussi aux commandes de mechas. Pilotez des véhicules ou usez juste de vos armes pour exploser les BattleMech d'en face. Enfin, prouvez votre valeur sur le Xbox Live via des affrontements en ligne.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/MechAssault 2 - Lone Wolf (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/MechAssault 2 - Lone Wolf (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/MechAssault 2 - Lone Wolf (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Day 1 Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2-12</players>
		<genreid>261</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15329" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Murakumo - Renegade Mech Pursuit (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Murakumo</name>
		<desc>Murakumo est un jeu de combats de robots géants sorti sur Xbox. Choisissez votre mécha parmi une petite tripotée puis partez en mission de poursuite et de destruction. Chaque réussite vous débloque un mécha plus puissant.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Murakumo - Renegade Mech Pursuit (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Murakumo - Renegade Mech Pursuit (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Murakumo - Renegade Mech Pursuit (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20030305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>From Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="14862" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Otogi - Myth of Demons (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Otogi : Myth of Demons</name>
		<desc>Otogi : Myth of Demons est un jeu d'action sorti sur Xbox. Contrôlez un guerrier vampire coincé entre la vie et la mort et parcourez les 25 niveaux de ce jeu prenant place dans l'ancien Japon. Vous pourrez faire évoluer votre personnage grâce aux éléments de jeu de rôle implantés.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Otogi - Myth of Demons (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Otogi - Myth of Demons (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Otogi - Myth of Demons (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="14936" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Otogi 2 - Immortal Warriors (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Otogi 2 : Immortal Warriors</name>
		<desc>Otogi 2 : Immortal Warriors sur Xbox est un jeu d'action emprunt de mysticisme bien oriental. Le guerrier Raikoh reprend du service, avec 5 compagnons, dans le massacre de démons et autres créatures infernales. A la fois poétique et violent, l'univers du jeu vous offre de parcourir de nombreux paysages, de la plaine désolée à la forêt, afin d'occire ces rejetons de l'Enfer.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Otogi 2 - Immortal Warriors (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Otogi 2 - Immortal Warriors (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Otogi 2 - Immortal Warriors (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>263</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15224" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Outlaw Volleyball (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Outlaw Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Outlaw Volleyball is the second game in Simon &amp; Schuster's growing Outlaw franchise.



As the title suggests, you play various games of volleyball with shady and dirty characters, from a slutty biker to an ex con to a pair of strippers. There are sixteen players in total. Each character has his or her own unique personality, strengths and weaknesses.



There are four different modes you can compete in; Exhibition, which is a standard volleyball game, Tour, which is the career mode that spans fifty different events, and Drills, which are sort of like practice games that awards points you can use to improve your player's abilities. The fourth mode is Xbox Live enabled, allowing you to play with people over the Xbox Live service.



There are ten different courts to play on, each one with it's own backgrounds and animation. You can play on a beach, at a carnival, or even in a prison.



Outlaw Volleyball utilizes the same momentum feature first seen in Outlaw Golf, which allows you to earn "beating tokens" that you can spend on beating up the other team. If you are doing lousy, beating up a member of the other team refills your momentum meter, allowing you to come back and possibly win.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Outlaw Volleyball (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Outlaw Volleyball (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outlaw Volleyball (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hypnotix</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<genreid>1536</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14890" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Phantom Dust (Japan) (Taikenban).iso</path>
		<name>Phantom Dust</name>
		<desc>Le jeu d'action Phantom Dust sur Xbox se déroule dans un monde post-apocalyptique où une étrange poussière est tombée du ciel en ôtant la mémoire à tout le monde. Un groupe d'humains ayant développé des pouvoirs surnaturels, les Espers, ont découvert deux corps dans des capsules d'hibernation. L'un des deux se nomme Edgar, et pourrait détenir des informations cruciales sur la poussière de fantôme. L'autre, c'est vous.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Phantom Dust (Japan) (Taikenban).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Phantom Dust (Japan) (Taikenban).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Phantom Dust (Japan) (Taikenban).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20040923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15601" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sneakers (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sneakers</name>
		<desc>Get ready for a fun adventure filled with cartoon combat. In Sneakers, you play Apollo, a mouse who must lead his friends through a human-sized town to battle the enemy. You must protect your troops by directing their actions and throwing wind-up punches and flying kicks. While your small size lets you take shortcuts through small holes in the wall, it also makes a rolling apple as dangerous as a tumbling boulder. Only those with cunning and quick minds can leave victoriously.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sneakers (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sneakers (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sneakers (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20021022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Media Vision</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<genreid>2816</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15355" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Spikeout Battle Street</name>
		<desc>Spikeout : Battle Street est un jeu beat'em all sur Xbox. Rien ne va plus sur l'île de Diesel Town, la criminalité ravage la ville, les habitants sont terrorisés... Ah là là, heureusement que vous êtes là ! Sous la traveste de Spike Jr, vous allez devoir botter les fesses de moult malfrats en mal de corrections. Le tout dans un pantalon moulant rose bonbon...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<genreid>263</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14792" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars - Obi-Wan (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Obi-Wan</name>
		<desc>Star Wars : Obi-Wan est un jeu d'action sur Xbox qui vous place dans la peau de Obi-Wan Kenobi. Le titre propose cinq chapitres ponctués par diverses missions et différents Jedis à affronter au cours d'entraînements. Votre but est de déjouer les plans de la fédération du commerce, le soft reprend donc dans les grandes lignes l'Episode 1. Un mode duel est à votre disposition pour affronter un de vos amis dans des combats épiques.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Obi-Wan (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Obi-Wan (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Obi-Wan (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20011219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<genreid>512</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14873" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Steel Battalion (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Steel Battalion</name>
		<desc>Power up your Vertical Tank, and prepare to dominate the online arena. In the midst of a volatile military coup, you must master the inner workings of your VT using the Steel Battalion controller. Up to 10 players can battle head-to-head in team or solo deathmatch games. Complete operations in Campaign mode or play free mission games such as Battle Royale, Conquest, or Capture the Container. The military dynamic of the game constantly changes with Xbox Live, making Steel Battalion Online one intense futuristic combat game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Steel Battalion (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Steel Battalion (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Steel Battalion (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14899" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Superman - The Man of Steel (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Superman : The Man of Steel</name>
		<desc>Superman : The Man of Steel est un jeu d'action sur Xbox dans lequel vous incarnez le héros en collant mieux connu sous le nom de Superman. Le jeu est tiré des comics originaux, vous retrouvez donc de nombreuses connaissances comme par exemple Lex Luthor, Byzaro et Brainiac. Participez à des combats au sol ou aériens dans Metropolis, la zone fantôme, l'hyperespace ou encore beaucoup d'autres environnements.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Superman - The Man of Steel (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Superman - The Man of Steel (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Superman - The Man of Steel (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Circus Freak</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="15365" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Xyanide (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).iso</path>
		<name>Xyanide</name>
		<desc>Xyanide sur Xbox est un shoot'em up doté d'une histoire particulière, puisque vous évoluez dans un univers complexe, fait des pensées d'une enfant pas très sympathique. A vous de vous débarrasser des hordes d'ennemis qu'elle vous envoie à la figure, le tout dans des décors psychédéliques et biomécaniques.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Xyanide (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Xyanide (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Xyanide (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060815T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playlogic</developer>
		<publisher>Playlogic</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<genreid>260</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15121" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yager (Europe) (En Fr De).iso</path>
		<name>Yager</name>
		<desc>Yager est un jeu de tir sur Xbox. Vous incarnez Magnus Tide, pilote de combat, dans un XIXème siècle tourmenté par la guerre, les luttes de pouvoir et les conspirations. Prenez place dans un vaisseau futuriste : le Sagittarius dont l'arsenal s'étoffe tout le long de l'aventure. Des combats aériens ravageurs vous attendent dans les cieux de Yager au travers de plus de 20 missions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Yager (Europe) (En Fr De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Yager (Europe) (En Fr De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yager (Europe) (En Fr De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<genreid>261</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14830" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeons and Dragons - Heroes (Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Dungeons &amp; Dragons Heroes</name>
		<desc>Dungeons &amp; Dragons Heroes est un hack and slash sorti sur Xbox. Vous pouvez choisir un des quatre personnages jouables et surtout demander à des amis de vous rejoindre car ce jeu est jouable à 4 simultanément en coopération.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Heroes (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Heroes (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Heroes (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Hunt Valley Development Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<genreid>768</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neighbours from Hell (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Neighbours From Hell</name>
		<desc>Neighbours from Hell is a strategy video game for Nintendo GameCube, Microsoft Windows, and Xbox. In Europe, it was released for Windows on June 20, 2003, and the GameCube and Xbox on March 4, 2005. The game was released for Windows in the United States on September 22, 2003.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Neighbours from Hell (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Neighbours from Hell (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neighbours from Hell (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20051117T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Petit Copter (Japan).iso</path>
		<name>Petit Copter</name>
		<desc>R/C helicopter sim game by Aquasystem that invites players to explore indoor environments in tiny remote-control helicopters. There are two main modes: Challenge Mode basically throws a number of mini-game tasks the player's way, such landing and taking off from a heliport, shooting targets, competing in time attack challenges, and so forth. In Adventure mode, players hunt for stars, hidden in a variety of real-life environments, such as under kitchen tables, in a bathroom shelf, and on top of stereo speakers in the living room.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Petit Copter (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snap/Petit Copter (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Petit Copter (Japan).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20020520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AquaSystem Co.</developer>
		<publisher>AquaSystem</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>248acfe708ae22e5791679c50801c8ff</md5>
	</game>
	<game id="15035" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Blood Wake (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Blood Wake</name>
		<desc>Blood Wake est un jeu d'action sur Xbox. Naviguez sur la Mer des Dragons à bord de votre bateau ultra rapide et surarmé et coulez tous ceux qui auront l'audace de se mettre en travers de votre chemin. Y compris vos amis en mode multijoueur jusqu'à 4.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blood Wake (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blood Wake (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blood Wake (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stormfront Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Black.iso</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Black</name>
		<desc>Ninja Gaiden Black and Ninja Gaiden Sigma. The game follows the fictional story of Ryu Hayabusa, a master ninja, in his quest to recover a stolen sword and avenge the slaughter of his clan.



Tecmo specifically targeted Ninja Gaiden at a non-Japanese audience, and despite difficulties in obtaining content ratings due to the game's graphic depictions of violence, it was generally well received, and 362,441 copies were sold in North America in the first month after its release. Nevertheless, the game had to be censored for release in some regions, and Japanese sales were poor, with only 60,000 in the four months following its release. Making use of the Xbox's internet connectivity, Ninja Gaiden was the focus of a series of online contests across North America, Europe and Japan. Record-breaking numbers of players took part, competing for places in the live final, which was held during the Tokyo Game Show (TGS) 2004.



Team Ninja continued to update the game after its release: two Hurricane Packs were made available as free downloadable content that added extra content, gameplay challenges, and game engine improvements.[1] These were incorporated into a reworked version, released in 2005 and entitled Ninja Gaiden Black, that was regarded by the game's creator Tomonobu Itagaki and many players as the definitive version. In 2007, Ninja Gaiden was graphically enhanced on the PlayStation 3, with extra content, in the form of Ninja Gaiden Sigma. This version was later released on the PlayStation Vita as Ninja Gaiden Sigma Plus.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ninja Gaiden Black.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ninja Gaiden Black.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ninja Gaiden Black.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14796" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sega GT 2002 (USA) (En Ja).iso</path>
		<name>Sega Gt 2002</name>
		<desc>Sega GT 2002 est un jeu de courses sur Xbox qui offre différents modes de jeu tels que la Course rapide, le Chronicle ainsi que le mode Carrière dans lequel vous devez tenter de remporter le plus de courses pour pouvoir acheter de nouvelles voitures ou personnaliser celles que vous possédez déjà. Sega GT 2002 est jouable à deux en écran séparé.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sega GT 2002 (USA) (En Ja).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sega GT 2002 (USA) (En Ja).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sega GT 2002 (USA) (En Ja).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Soccer Slam.iso</path>
		<name>Sega Soccer Slam</name>
		<desc>Hidden away in underground leagues and counter-culture clubs, Sega introduces a brutal new brand of soccer. Played by thugs who kick ass on and off the field, participants opt to watch their backs and let the crowds watch the game. Since nastiness supplants sportsmanship in this 3-on-3 hybrid of the world's most popular sport, the rulebook is only good as a splint for broken bones.



Given its rule-bending recipe, Soccer Slam is an exciting and original game, in which individual achievement prevails over teamwork while gameplay focuses on speed, skill, and aggression. This means that players don't just take on the competition, they take 'em out!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sega Soccer Slam.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sega Soccer Slam.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sega Soccer Slam.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts, Black Box</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2X.iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2X</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2x was designed to take full advantage of the technical capabilities of Xbox. The game features the franchise's signature gameplay, intuitive controls, all of the levels from both Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 and the original Tony Hawk's Pro Skater, in addition to more populated environments, brand new levels, realistic special effects and smoother lifelike animations. The inclusion of system link gameplay brings the skateboarding experience to life.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2X.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2X.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2X.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20011114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3.iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>You may not be able to live like the legend, but now you can skate like him. Skate as the legendary Tony Hawk or choose from a dream team of 12 top pro skaters, including old favorites like Lasek, Thomas, Muska, and Steamer, as well as new talent like Gilfberg, Caballero, Koston, and Mullen. Or enjoy full customization abilities with the enhanced Create-a-Skater (now including female skaters) and the Skatepark Editor. Travel from L.A. to Tokyo, Suburbia to Skater's Island performing challenges and meeting goals. New moves include the Revert, which allows you to link vert tricks, and flatland tricks such as Caspers, the Primo, and Handstand Manual. If you're good, you can even unlock hidden pro footage.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT - Mutant Melee.iso</path>
		<name>TMNT: Mutant Melee</name>
		<desc>Run with the Turtles as they trash, smash and bash their way to victory in the ultimate 4 player Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles action game!



-Over 20 playable characters

-Unpredictable obstacles around every corner

-Melee and Adventure Mode

-A wide range of mini games including Last Man Standing, King of the Hill and more!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TMNT - Mutant Melee.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TMNT - Mutant Melee.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TMNT - Mutant Melee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20050315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Hawaii</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT 3 - Mutant Nightmare.iso</path>
		<name>TMNT 3: Mutant Nightmare</name>
		<desc>TMNT3 puts more of a focus on teamwork, character development and control than any other console Turtles game to date. Gamers can play as their favorite Turtle alone or with up to three friends, earning experience points along the way as they slash and bash Foot Ninjas and powerful, well-known bosses from the TMNT universe. These experience points allow players to improve and evolve their Turtles' traits and abilities for more varied, powerful attacks and moves. The Ninja Scroll System is another new feature on TMMT3. Being able to select which ninja scrolls to use allows the Turtles to use various special abilities strategically. Cooperative play lies at the heart of TMNT3 and gamers who team up with friends for multiplayer action are rewarded with exclusive features such as Cooperative Attack for even more shell shocking damage to enemies. The effect of this attack changes depending on the number of players working together (between 2-4 players). For even greater control, TMNT3 features a new combat system called the Target Attack system that lets gamers play more instinctively and strategically. With the Target Attack system, players will be able to lock onto specific enemies and block, dodge or counter attack accordingly for smoother and more maneuverable combat. Story Mode can be played with 1-4 players. Even when you have less than 4 players to play, the other Turtles will be at your side, controlled through AI. All the Turtles can participate in Cooperative Attack to beat enemies and players can give commands to the AI.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TMNT 3 - Mutant Nightmare.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TMNT 3 - Mutant Nightmare.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TMNT 3 - Mutant Nightmare.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AMF Bowling 2004.iso</path>
		<name>AMF Bowling 2004</name>
		<desc>Bowling fans can appreciate AMF Bowling 2004's realistic sound effects, array of gameplay options, and accurate ball, pin, and lane physics. This bowling simulation also lets you create your own bowler and customize your ball's weight, color, and texture. In multiple gameplay modes, such as practice and tournament play, you can find that perfect combination of position, speed, and ball velocity. Showcase your skills against professional bowlers or against a friend.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AMF Bowling 2004.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AMF Bowling 2004.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AMF Bowling 2004.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20031114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mud Duck Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Jack of All Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Genma Onimusha.iso</path>
		<name>Genma Onimusha</name>
		<desc>Onimusha: Warlords, released in Japan as Onimusha (鬼武者?), is the first action-adventure video game of the Onimusha series, released first for the PlayStation 2 in 2001. Later it was released in an updated form as Genma Onimusha (幻魔 鬼武者?) for the Xbox in 2002. The original Onimusha: Warlords version was also ported to Microsoft Windows, although this version was only released in Asia and Russia.



The game's plot is set in the Sengoku period and focuses on the samurai Samanosuke Akechi who fights against the forces of Nobunaga Oda. After Nobunaga's death in battle, Samanosuke goes on a quest to save Princess Yuki from demons working alongside Nobunaga's forces. The player controls Samanosuke and his partner, a female ninja Kaede, in their fight against demons.



While the game borrows elements from Capcom's own Resident Evil survival horror series, such as solving puzzles and a fixed camera, the game is focused more on the action genre with Samanosuke possessing multiple weapons that can be upgraded by defeating several enemies. Capcom originally wanted to release the game for the original PlayStation but the close release of its next generation version resulting in the project being scrapped.



Following its release, Onimusha: Warlords achieved high popularity becoming the first PlayStation 2 game to reach the one million sales. Its sales eventually surpassed the two million units worldwide. The game has been well received by video game publications and has been recognized as one of the best titles on the system. It also spanned two direct sequels for the same console and another three games within the franchise.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Genma Onimusha.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Genma Onimusha.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Genma Onimusha.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="204068" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crusty Demons (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Crusty Demons</name>
		<image>./mixart/Crusty Demons (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Crusty Demons (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crusty Demons (USA).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060627T000000</releasedate>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball.iso</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive: Xtreme Beach Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Are you ready for some extreme action?  Then your wait is over because the girls of Dead or Alive are back and better than ever in the first ever "Sports Fantasy Simulation."  Developed by Team Ninja, the guys who brought you the million-selling Dead or Alive 3 fighting game, Dead or Alive Xtreme Beach Volleyball is sure to have your heart racing with beautifully rendered graphics and action-packed gameplay.  The extreme action is transported from the fighting ring of Dead or Alive 3 to the beach this time around with the girls throwing on their bikinis to go head-to-head in the most outrageous beach volleyball game you have ever seen!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20030122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="15527" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kakuto Chojin (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Kakuto Chojin : Back Alley Brutal</name>
		<desc>Kakuto Chojin sur Xbox est un jeu qui met en scène des combats de rue. Incarnez 12 personnages différents ayant chacun son propre style. Les réactions de vos personnages varieront selon les coups portés rendant chaque combat unique.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kakuto Chojin (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Kakuto Chojin (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kakuto Chojin (USA).jpg</marquee>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MTVs Celebrity Deathmatch.iso</path>
		<name>MTV Celebrity Deathmatch</name>
		<desc>Based on the TV show, MTV's Celebrity Deathmatch pits famous personalities against each other in bloody bouts. Each of the 15 characters has their own special moves and reflects the damage taken during fights with bruises, blood, dents, and deformities. You can also create your own celebrity and test his or her skills in the arena spotlight. Original show hosts Nick Diamond and Johnny Gomez provide color commentary while referee Mills Lane calls the shots.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/MTVs Celebrity Deathmatch.png</image>
		<video>./snap/MTVs Celebrity Deathmatch.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/MTVs Celebrity Deathmatch.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20031014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Ape Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Gotham Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - Nightfire.iso</path>
		<name>007: NightFire</name>
		<desc>NightFire will feature an original single player storyline -- written exclusively for the game and borrowing from the rich 007-legacy that spans 40 years. As Bond, players will operate in the snow capped Austrian Alps and the far reaches of outer space as well as underwater in the depths of the South Pacific to defeat the evil criminal mastermind Rafael Drake, the popular head of a supposedly benign environmental organization who secretly is bent on world domination.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/007 - Nightfire.png</image>
		<video>./snap/007 - Nightfire.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/007 - Nightfire.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Amped 2.iso</path>
		<name>Amped 2</name>
		<desc>Amped 2 is the ultimate freestyle experience, offering the largest, most varied trick library of any snowboarding game. Explore vast areas of wide-open, spectacularly rendered real mountains packed with terrain parks designed by world-famous snow park architect, Chris Gunnarson. Play head-to-head with friends in the various multiplayer modes. When you're ready to take it to the next level, connect to Xbox Live to check rankings and challenge the world's best virtual riders.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Amped 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Amped 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Amped 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indie Built</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis.iso</path>
		<name>Aquaman: Battle for Atlantis</name>
		<desc>Here's your chance to wield the power of Aquaman, the DC Comics superhero, as he defends the deep-sea city of Atlantis against such enemies as Ocean Master, Black Manta, and the Lava Lord of the Fire Trolls. You must fight to save the lost city by using Aquaman's super powers, telepathy, and hook-hand. While the game features plenty of intense underwater battles, you can also bombard your enemies from an attack sub in first-person mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucky Chicken Games</developer>
		<publisher>TDK Mediactive, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battlestar Galactica.iso</path>
		<name>Battlestar Galactica</name>
		<desc>The war between man and machine rages on as the mechanical Cylons return to wipe out the human race. Begin your heroic journey through the Battlestar Galactica universe as the fearless, young Adama, and help lead the fleet of Colonials to survival. Choose from a wide array of ships, from sleek Vipers to heavy Bombers, and engage various classes of Cylon vessels, including Raiders and Marauders.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Battlestar Galactica.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Battlestar Galactica.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Battlestar Galactica.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warthog</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Halo - Combat Evolved.iso</path>
		<name>Halo: Combat Evolved (PAL)</name>
		<desc>Halo: Combat Evolved is a 2001 first-person shooter science-fiction video game developed by Bungie Studios and the first game in the Halo series. It focuses on John-117 and the crew of the UNSC Pillar of Autumn who, fleeing from the Fall of Reach, stumble on the Forerunner Halo Installation 04, only to be forced into a desperate battle against the Covenant and the Flood. Considered a classic, Combat Evolved is one of the most popular video games for the Xbox with eight million copies sold. Its sales are rivaled only by its sequels, Halo 2 and Halo 3.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Halo - Combat Evolved.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Halo - Combat Evolved.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halo - Combat Evolved.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bungie</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Guy Game.iso</path>
		<name>The Guy Game</name>
		<desc>The Guy Game is an adult video game for the PlayStation 2, Xbox and PC platforms published in 2004 by Gathering of Developers and developed by now-defunct Top Heavy Studios (it was the team's only game). Presented in a trivia gameshow style supporting up to four players, it consists of about 1,000 questions spread out over 20 episodes. Much of the game involves watching live-action video footage of young women in bikinis, and as the player succeeds in the game the women eventually expose their breasts. The game garnered much controversy and was the subject of a lawsuit.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Guy Game.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The Guy Game.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Guy Game.png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20040830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Topheavy</developer>
		<publisher>Gathering of Developers</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="15287" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ultimate Pro Pinball (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Ultimate Pro Pinball</name>
		<desc>Ultimate Pro Pinball sur Xbox est un jeu de flipper vous proposant un choix de trois tableaux différents. Vous savez, ces machines emblématiques des bistrots qui engloutissaient avidement nos pièces de monnaie alors qu'on essayait encore et toujours d'obtenir la fatidique "extra ball"...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ultimate Pro Pinball (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ultimate Pro Pinball (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ultimate Pro Pinball (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atomic Planet</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>1792</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Summit.iso</path>
		<name>Dark Summit</name>
		<desc>Snowboarders have never felt welcome on Mt. Garrick, a once quiet and peaceful ski resort. Chief O' Leary, the resident ranger, has led the charge against boarders and limited their access to certain sections of the mountain. But the situation has progressed. Chief O'Leary has mysteriously closed the summit to all boarders and is trying desperately to drive them off the mountain.

 Shred, jib and stomp sick tricks in the first</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dark Summit.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dark Summit.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dark Summit.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="15586">
		<path>./Triple Play 2002 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Triple Play 2002</name>
		<desc>Step up to the plate and swing for the fences with Triple Play 2002 for the Xbox. The action on the field comes to life with real player models and dramatic out-of-play sequences, giving players the chance to experience big game moments such as a game-winning hit or a key strikeout.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Triple Play 2002 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Triple Play 2002 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Triple Play 2002 (USA).png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20020318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15305">
		<path>./Alter Echo.iso</path>
		<name>Alter Echo</name>
		<desc>In Alter Echo, interstellar corporations mine a new organic skin called Plast and use it to make biomachines. Nevin, who can physically alter Plast and time itself, discovers that illegal experiments have infected Plast with human consciousness, and now he must fight for survival against a world gone mad. As you battle wave after wave of biomechanical enemies, you can morph between Melee, Gun, and Stealth modes. A Time Dilation system allows players to freeze the action and cue up an unstoppable flurry of moves and special attacks.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Alter Echo.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Alter Echo.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Alter Echo.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20030819T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Outrage Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="15249" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Armed and Dangerous.iso</path>
		<name>Armed And Dangerous</name>
		<desc>Take a band of gun-toting rebels - a robot, a madman, a mole and a criminal mastermind. Put them in a vividly stunning fantasy realm. Then give them an impossible mission - pulling off the biggest heist of all time in the middle of a war. All you have to do is battle your way through dastardly enemies, giant war machines and an army of psychopathic robots. But don't worry; you have plenty of ammo and absolutely no common sense. Victory is yours in 12,000 bullets or less!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Armed and Dangerous.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Armed and Dangerous.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Armed and Dangerous.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Planet Moon</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14951" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Aliens Versus Predator Extinction.iso</path>
		<name>Aliens versus Predator : Extinction</name>
		<desc>The battle that has split more blood over centuries continues, with the human marines caught in-between the powerful Aliens and the deadly Predators. Extinction has you controlling one of the three races in a real time strategy mix, building each unit and setting them out into the battlefield to complete a range of tasks. Each race has an advantage and disadvantage. The humans have a collection of different units, from heavy weapons experts to medics, and are better known for their long range attacks. Predators are hardcore fighters, taking the battle right up to the enemy, although there are fewer of them available to counter act their superior power. Finally, the Aliens are fast and deadly, and always hunt in large packs.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aliens Versus Predator Extinction.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aliens Versus Predator Extinction.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aliens Versus Predator Extinction.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20030808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zono</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<genreid>1280</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outlaw Golf 2.iso</path>
		<name>Outlaw Golf 2</name>
		<desc>The crude cast of Outlaw Golf is back with new friends, courses, fighting moves, and more. Choose from 11 wild characters--including babes, rappers, and thugs--and take on the challenges from eight courses, ranging from the arctic to the jungle. By playing through the tour and winning events, you can unlock more clubs, balls, and outfits. In addition to tournament mode, the game features match, time attack, and baseball golf modes. Just remember--even if your golf game is off, you can still beat up your opponents, or even your caddy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Outlaw Golf 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Outlaw Golf 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outlaw Golf 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20041019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hypnotix</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker Live and Reloaded.iso</path>
		<name>Conker: Live &amp; Reloaded</name>
		<desc>Conker, gaming’s notoriously naughty squirrel, arrives on the Xbox with a bang in an all-new Xbox Live-enabled team-based shooter, Conker: Live and Reloaded.



The game features intense Deathmatch and Campaign story line modes via Xbox Live and System Link, and players can compete as one of six combat specialists across multi-mission campaigns covering Old War and Future War. The warfare promises to deliver the non-stop action, humor, and innuendos Conker is famous for.



Also included is the critically acclaimed single-player game, Conker’s Bad Fur Day, completely recreated for the Xbox with stunning graphics and unparalleled attitude.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Conker Live and Reloaded.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Conker Live and Reloaded.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Conker Live and Reloaded.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crimson Skies - High Road to Revenge.iso</path>
		<name>Crimson Skies: High Road To Revenge</name>
		<desc>Crimson Skies: High Road to Revenge combines thrilling aerial combat with the swashbuckling style of a Hollywood action-adventure movie. Set in an alternate 1930s world of gunship diplomacy and sinister intrigue, the game lets you pilot powerful aircraft--armed with detonator cannons, tesla guns, or remote-controlled rockets--against nefarious air pirates and behemoth war zeppelins. As the daring air pirate Nathan Zachary, leader of the infamous Fortune Hunters, you take off on a high-flying adventure, filled with daring escapes and damsels in distress.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crimson Skies - High Road to Revenge.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Crimson Skies - High Road to Revenge.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crimson Skies - High Road to Revenge.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FASA Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14663" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Forza Motorsport (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt,Zh,Ko) (v1.70).iso</path>
		<name>Forza Motorsport</name>
		<desc>Racing sim from Microsoft, targeted at gamers who are passionate about cars and racing. Own, customize, and race your favorite cars in the most technologically advanced and realistic driving sim yet. Use race earnings to buy upgrades and aftermarket parts, so you can transform real production cars into high-performance racers. On the track, experience an impressively accurate simulation, while putting your performance-tuned creations to the test against the online gaming world on Xbox Live. Features car models from more than 60 top car manufacturers, customization via decals and team paint-schemes, and vehicle tuning that really affects performance.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Forza Motorsport (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt,Zh,Ko) (v1.70).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Forza Motorsport (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt,Zh,Ko) (v1.70).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Forza Motorsport (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt,Zh,Ko) (v1.70).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Dragoon Orta.iso</path>
		<name>Panzer Dragoon Orta</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment of the Panzer Dragoon series has you playing Orta, a young girl who has been imprisoned by the Empire. Under a wave of attack, the prison camp is broken through by a mysterious dragon, and Orta takes it upon herself to ride the dragon, and destroy the Empire once and for all. Along the way, she will also discover her own destiny, and the mystery surrounding her new friend.



Simply put, you have limited control of the dragon for most of the game, as your trigger finger will be shooting non-stop at the enemies that fly around the area. Orta will be your main source of fire-power when you simply press the fire button, but by pressing and holding, the aim cursor will change, allowing you to fire a burst of power from the dragon at whatever the cursor aims at.



The dragon itself can change into three forms at a press of a button. Each form has a different style of attack and power ability.



A port of the original Panzer Dragoon is included.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Panzer Dragoon Orta.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Panzer Dragoon Orta.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Panzer Dragoon Orta.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pure Pinball.iso</path>
		<name>Pure Pinball</name>
		<desc>Pure Pinball is a pinball simulation video game developed by Iridon Interactive (now Legendo Entertainment) and published in North America by Simon &amp; Schuster for the Microsoft Windows and XS Games for the Xbox, released on May 28, 2003 and August 5, 2004, respectively. The game was published in Europe by Iridon Interactive and distributed by Koch Media in Germany.[1][2]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pure Pinball.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pure Pinball.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pure Pinball.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20040805T000000</releasedate>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TaoFang - Fist of the Lotus.iso</path>
		<name>Tao Feng: Fist of the Lotus</name>
		<desc>Clothes will tear, blood will spill, and bones will break in the brutal fighting game Tao Feng: Fist of the Lotus. On the vicious streets and back-alleyways of New China, two fierce fighting sects battle in a race to uncover a valuable prize. During your fights throughout interactive environments, your fighter reflects all the physical damage he or she receives from opponents. You can either heal yourself from the beatings or build your powers to unleash devastating Chi attacks.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TaoFang - Fist of the Lotus.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TaoFang - Fist of the Lotus.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TaoFang - Fist of the Lotus.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20030318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Gigante</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The House Of The Dead 3.iso</path>
		<name>The House of the Dead III</name>
		<desc>The House of the Dead III is a 2002 light gun arcade game with a horror zombie-survival theme, and the third installment to the House of the Dead series of video games, developed by Wow Entertainment and Sega. It was later ported to the Xbox in 2003, Microsoft Windows in 2005, the Wii in 2008 in a compilation with The House of the Dead 2, and PlayStation 3 in 2012 with PlayStation Move support. The game continues the story of the previous games and introduces new gameplay concepts such as story branching. The game's protagonist is Lisa Rogan, daughter of Thomas Rogan, the first game's main character, and players control Lisa, G, or Daniel Curien.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The House Of The Dead 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The House Of The Dead 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The House Of The Dead 3.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20021024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WOW Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter, Horror</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Blinx - The Time Sweeper (Japan) (En,Ja).iso</path>
		<name>Blinx : The Time Sweeper</name>
		<desc>Blinx: The Time Sweeper is a fast-paced action game featuring a cool, clever new character in wild, warped worlds. The ability to control the flow of time provides a totally new 4-dimensional gaming experience only possible on Xbox.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blinx - The Time Sweeper (Japan) (En,Ja).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blinx - The Time Sweeper (Japan) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blinx - The Time Sweeper (Japan) (En,Ja).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20021212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Artoon</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp,en</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<genreid>257</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14844" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Breakdown (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Breakdown</name>
		<desc>Breakdown is unique in that it is technically categorized as a first-person shooter, but integrates the experiences of a fighting game into the experience as well as using auto-lock-on for shooting enemies. The viewpoint never leaves the perspective of the player, and interaction with objects, reloading of guns, and the impact of hitting the floor are all seen through this first-person perspective. Unlike other first-person shooters, interaction with objects is also all done in a realistic manner in Breakdown; ammunition is picked up by looking down and grabbing it with your arm instead of walking over it, similarly doors are opened by grabbing the handle, key cards used by swiping them over a scanner, ladders by using the arms for climbing and many others. Health and energy are replenished by consuming energy bars, sodas and hamburgers, which the player must eat while remaining in first person.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Breakdown (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Breakdown (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Breakdown (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14754" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Brute Force (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Brute Force</name>
		<desc>Brute Force is a video game released for the Xbox by Microsoft in 2003. The game is a squad-based third-person shooter that uses four members of a team which fight in numerous battles. Each character on the team has their own strengths and weaknesses. The story is of a science-fiction setting where humans spread throughout the galaxy and tension arises with the threat of a hostile alien race that appears. The squad, Brute Force, is sent in to confront the enemy. Brute Force began as a PC game in 2000, but was soon after turned into a first-party title for the Xbox, following the buyout of Digital Anvil by Microsoft.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Brute Force (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Brute Force (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Brute Force (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<players>28</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14721" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Call of Cthulhu - Dark Corners of the Earth (Europe) (En,Fr,De).iso</path>
		<name>Call of Cthulhu : Dark Corners of the Earth</name>
		<desc>Detective Jack Walters arrived in Innsmouth to solve a case of a missing person. But soon he finds himself confronted with terrible mysteries older than humanity, and with ghosts of the mysterious events that led to his incarceration in a mental hospital years ago.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Call of Cthulhu - Dark Corners of the Earth (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Call of Cthulhu - Dark Corners of the Earth (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Call of Cthulhu - Dark Corners of the Earth (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2K Games</developer>
		<publisher>Headfirst</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>256</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15097" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crazy Taxi 3 - High Roller (Japan) (En,Ja).iso</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi 3</name>
		<desc>Crazy Taxi 3 sur Xbox est un jeu de voiture permettant de piloter un taxi à travers une ville fictive. Troisième opus de la série, le but du jeu est de conduire les nombreux clients à leur lieu de destination respectif en un temps imparti dans une ville où tout vous est permis... Autrement dit, vous pouvez d'ores et déjà oublier le code de la route !</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crazy Taxi 3 - High Roller (Japan) (En,Ja).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Crazy Taxi 3 - High Roller (Japan) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crazy Taxi 3 - High Roller (Japan) (En,Ja).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20031023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp,en</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14705" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dead or Alive 3.iso</path>
		<name>Dead Or Alive 3</name>
		<desc>Dead or Alive 3 (Japanese: ?3 Hepburn: Deddo Oa Araibu Sur, abbreviated as DOA3 ) is a fighting game in the Dead or Alive series. It was released in 2001, exclusively on the Xbox as a launch title.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead or Alive 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead or Alive 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead or Alive 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20020314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<genreid>262</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="15074" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Deathrow (Europe) (En Fr De).iso</path>
		<name>Deathrow</name>
		<desc>Enter a brutal fighting sport where only the fastest and toughest players are victorious. Deathrow combines the fast gameplay of third-person action games, the intensity of fighting games, and the cooperative team play and gritty roughness of rugby. The object of Deathrow is to win matches by any means necessary, either by scoring as many points as possible before time runs out or by severely injuring your opponents and removing them from the field of combat. Engage in fierce hand-to-hand combat against your friends, enemies, or intelligent AI opponents that don't just get mad--they get even.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Deathrow (Europe) (En Fr De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Deathrow (Europe) (En Fr De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Deathrow (Europe) (En Fr De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Southend Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>1536</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14737">
		<path>./Deus Ex - Invisible War (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Deus Ex : Invisible War</name>
		<desc>Twenty years have passed after the events described in Deus Ex. The actions of JC Denton have eventually led to a period of economic depression, known as "The Collapse". The world is on the brink of chaos after the dismantling of the mighty biotech corporations, and multiple religious and political groups lust after power.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Deus Ex - Invisible War (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Deus Ex - Invisible War (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Deus Ex - Invisible War (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20031202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ion Storm</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15060" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Galleon (Europe) (En Fr De).iso</path>
		<name>Galleon</name>
		<desc>Galleon sur Xbox est un jeu d'action/aventure ancré dans l'univers de la piraterie. Embarquez pour une quête et découvrez les origines d'un mystérieux navire qui pourrait bien cacher la clé d'un pouvoir. Participez à de nombreux combats contre des monstres et des créatures maléfiques dans une aventure qui ne s'annonce pas de tout repos.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Galleon (Europe) (En Fr De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Galleon (Europe) (En Fr De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Galleon (Europe) (En Fr De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCi Games</developer>
		<publisher>Confounding Factor</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>512</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14774" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kung Fu Chaos (Europe) (En,Fr,De).iso</path>
		<name>Kung Fu Chaos</name>
		<desc>Jouez les ninjas du dimanche dans ce party-game sorti sur Xbox. Kung Fu Chaos vous met dans la peau d'un acteur d'une vieille série des années 70 sur le kung fu. Suivez les directions du réalisateur et affrontez-vous à 4 dans des mini-jeux où l'humour est omniprésent.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kung Fu Chaos (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Kung Fu Chaos (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kung Fu Chaos (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030411T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Just Add Monsters</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>2304</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14648" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode III : La Revanche des Sith</name>
		<desc>Star Wars Episode III : La Revanche des Sith sur Xbox vous entraîne au coeur de la trame obscure du film, aux côtés d'Obi-wan Kenobi ou d'Anakin Skywalker. Force et sabres lasers seront de mise, face à des hordes d'ennemis prêts à en découdre. Votre personnage évolue grâce à des points d'expérience octroyés à la fin de chaque niveau.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<genreid>512</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14699">
		<path>./Arx Fatalis (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Arx Fatalis</name>
		<desc>Arx Fatalis is a partially open source first-person role-playing video game for the Xbox and Microsoft Windows, released on November 2002 by Arkane Studios, a video game developer based in Lyon, France.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Arx Fatalis (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Arx Fatalis (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Arx Fatalis (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arkane Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Dreamcatcher</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14876">
		<path>./Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Burnout 2 : Point Of Impact</name>
		<desc>Burnout is a street racing game focused around speed and crashing. Unlike many games which focus on closed course driving, you get to drive through cities with real traffic and city infrastructure. Designers have built city districts and surrounding areas, and implemented the race courses throughout the streets. As a result, many times certain parts of race-courses interlace with other parts of other races. As well, instead of encouraging strategic driving and safe driving, Burnout strongly encourages offensive driving. Driving on the wrong side of the road, barely missing passing traffic, drifting, and jumps all add to your boost "burnout" meter. Speed boosts and jumps aid your attempt to drive past buses, trucks and anything else that gets in the way. The more offensive and dangerous your driving is, the more boost you get!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Burnout</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14727">
		<path>./Burnout 3 - Takedown (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Burnout 3 : Takedown</name>
		<desc>Burnout 3: Takedown is a racing game which encourages aggressive driving and lets you use your vehicle to smash your way to the finish line by taking out your rivals and causing massive multi-car pileups. The more cars you take out, damage you inflict, the more events and cars you can unlock. Burnout 3 also has a "crash" mode which puts your vehicle at a variety of traffic junctions jam-packed with moving vehicles and pickups to see just how much monetary damage you can inflict.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Burnout 3 - Takedown (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Burnout 3 - Takedown (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Burnout 3 - Takedown (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Burnout</family>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15256">
		<path>./Close Combat - First to Fight - United States Marines (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Close Combat : First To Fight</name>
		<desc>Close Combat: First to Fight is a modern military first-person shooter. The player leads a marine fireteam in a fictional campaign taking place in Beirut, Lebanon. At certain times in the single player game, it's possible to call in mortar strikes and air strikes. Enemies have a psych-model similar to what is in the classic RTS Close Combat series, which causes them to hunker down, or even flee when they take enough fire. The game features four player co-op through the entire single player campaign, as well as multiplayer deathmatch. Available weapons are: M16A4, M203 Grenade Launcher, M249 SAW, M590 Shotgun, M67 Frag Grenade, M8HC Smoke Grenade, AK-74, SVD Sniper Rifle, M1911 Pistol, RPG-7, and RPK.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Close Combat - First to Fight - United States Marines (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Close Combat - First to Fight - United States Marines (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Close Combat - First to Fight - United States Marines (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Destineer</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15462">
		<path>./Combat - Task Force 121 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Combat : Task Force 121</name>
		<desc>In Combat: Task Force 121, you are a member of the elite Task Force 121, the US military force responsible for the capture of Saddam Hussein.  You are tasked with taking out a group of Marxist rebels intent on destabilizing the unnamed region.  The single player game takes takes you through an oil rig, dense jungles, a refinery, shanty towns and an exotic island. This FPS is very much a multiplayer oriented affair.  The game supports up to 16 players over Xbox Live, system link and Internet (PC).  There are 10 weapons to use, 10 multiplayer maps to explore and seven modes of play: deathmatch, team deathmatch, capture the flag, king of the hill, team king of the hill, last man standing, team last man standing and VIP escort.  There is also an offline training mode that lets you compete in deathmatch against bots.  The straightforward control scheme, well balanced weapons and interesting maps make for some quick, dirty and fun multiplayer action.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Combat - Task Force 121 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Combat - Task Force 121 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Combat - Task Force 121 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.1</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Direct Action Games</developer>
		<publisher>Zoo Digital Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15587">
		<path>./Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix</name>
		<desc>Dancing Stage Unleashed, or DS Unleashed, was released by Konami Digital Entertainment GmbH to the European Xbox audience on March 12, 2004. A sister release to the North American Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix, it features the same look and feel and the same options as Ultramix, including online play and content download through Xbox Live. Unleashed has a unique soundtrack and features music from Big Brovaz, Blondie and The Wonder Stuff as well as original tracks from Konami's in-house artists. The original release was followed by two sequels, Dancing Stage Unleashed 2 and 3, released May 13, 2005 and March 17, 2006 for the Xbox in Europe.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Hawaii</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Dance Dance Revolution</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15534">
		<path>./Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Dancing Stage Unleashed 2</name>
		<desc>Dancing Stage Unleashed 2 now features a wider range of Xbox Live modes. Via the online system, players can download new tracks, characters and challenge modes, and can also swap specially choreographed dance routines with like-minded fans. There is also an all-new 'Tournament' function wherein up to 8/16 users can participate in online 'dance-offs', with the greatest movers making it to a centrally housed Hall of Fame. Also, players can now play against dancing fans in the US, as well as their European counterparts.



Dancing Stage Unleashed 2 includes more than three dozen songs, of which 14 are licensed tracks, each of which is accompanied by its relevant promo video. The tracks in the new game span a range of decades and include 'Where's your head at' by Basement Jaxx and Girls Aloud's 'Love Machine' to cater for pop fans, while the likes of the classic 'Step On' by the Happy Mondays and 'Alright' by Supergrass offer a slice of the indie scene. A couple of true dance classics are also included in the shape of Donna Summer's 'Hot Stuff' and 'A Town Called Malice' by The Jam.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Hawaii</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Dance Dance Revolution</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15619">
		<path>./Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3</name>
		<desc>The third edition of DDR Ultramix, the title of DDR for XBOX, brings new features like new game modes as the Freestyle, Quest mode or Jukebox mode: Freestyle: allows players to dance just the way they want to any song in the game, while rewarding the completion of different combinations. Quest Mode: lets players travel “virtually” from city to city and build the ultimate dance team by completing challenging songs and routines along the way. Jukebox Mode turns your Xbox into a music machine allowing to listen the 65 default tracks and the downloables. Additionally, this edition includes 65 new songs (more knew, at least in EU) but DDRU3 is compatible with the downloaded song pack for the first and second part making more than 125 songs in total. Of course, the old game modes are present and you can still play the workout mode to make extra exercise or edit your songs to custom your playing. You can play trough Xbox Live until 4 ppls.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dance Dance Revolution Ultramix 3 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Hawaii</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Dance Dance Revolution</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14959">
		<path>./Dead to Rights.iso</path>
		<name>Dead To Rights</name>
		<desc>Meet Jack Slate, a cop framed for murder and facing execution. Slate escapes from Iron Point Maximum-Security Penitentiary to bring down the criminals that framed. In Dead to Rights, you play the role of Slate, as he fights through the hard streets and corrupt enemies of Grant City. There are plenty of ways go about bringing the conspirators to justice--Jack can perform disarm moves, shoot different weapons, pick locks, fight hand-to-hand, and play minigames such as arm wrestling, bench press, and dancing. In this gritty, crime-noir inspired epic, you're always on the run.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead to Rights.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead to Rights.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead to Rights.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020819T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14637">
		<path>./Doom 3 - Resurrection of Evil (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Doom 3 : Resurrection Of Evil</name>
		<desc>In this expansion pack for DOOM³, return to the devastated facilities on Mars (where the unexplained disaster took place two years prior) to find a beacon buried in the ruins. There are new enemies, weapons, locations and puzzles - and multiplayer for up to 8 players.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Doom 3 - Resurrection of Evil (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Doom 3 - Resurrection of Evil (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Doom 3 - Resurrection of Evil (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nerve Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Doom</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137575">
		<path>./Drake of the 99 Dragons (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Drake Of The 99 Dragons</name>
		<desc>The clan of the 99 Dragons has been wiped out and the artifact they had been guarding has fallen into the wrong hands. One of the clan members, Drake, is brought back from the dead to avenge his clan and recover the lost treasure.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Drake of the 99 Dragons (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Drake of the 99 Dragons (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Drake of the 99 Dragons (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20031103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Idol FX AB</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14610">
		<path>./Elder Scrolls III, The - Morrowind (USA) (Game of the Year Edition).iso</path>
		<name>The Elder Scrolls III : Morrowind</name>
		<desc>The Elder Scrolls III: Morrowind is an Xbox role-playing game that offers the player a lot of freedom. At the beginning you have to create a character by choosing among 10 races. Then you can decide whether to embark on the main quest or one of the many side quests offered. During your journeys you will meet many different creatures on which you can test your sword.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Elder Scrolls III, The - Morrowind (USA) (Game of the Year Edition).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Elder Scrolls III, The - Morrowind (USA) (Game of the Year Edition).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Elder Scrolls III, The - Morrowind (USA) (Game of the Year Edition).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14757">
		<path>./Enclave (USA) (En,Fr,De).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Enclave</name>
		<desc>In the fantasy world of Enclave, a bottomless rift divides the people of the Celenheim and the Outlands. Skirmishes along the border have become more and more frequent and it's only a matter of time before these altercations turn into a full-scale war. Now you must choose whether to lead the desperate people of Celenheim and save them from destruction, or ally with the dark hordes of the Outlands and overrun the Enclave. Whatever you decision, get ready for intense medieval combat featuring different playable characters, five mighty end bosses, and dozens of weapons, objects, and magical items.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Enclave (USA) (En,Fr,De).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Enclave (USA) (En,Fr,De).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Enclave (USA) (En,Fr,De).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Swing! Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Starbreeze Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14640">
		<path>./Far Cry Instincts (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Far Cry Instincts</name>
		<desc>The game follows the story of a man named Jack Carver. Carver is a former service member of the United States Navy, who was dishonorably discharged following a number of illegal actions. Afterwards, he sets up a shop in Manhattan and begins supplying illegal arms to anyone and everyone, until a gang performs a hit using weapons supplied by Jack against a Mafia heir. Consequently, a price is put on his head by the Mob, and he was forced to flee the United States and settle in Micronesia.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Far Cry Instincts (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Far Cry Instincts (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Far Cry Instincts (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Far Cry</family>
		<players>4-16</players>
		<lang>en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14902">
		<path>./Fight Night Round 3 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Fight Night : Round 3</name>
		<desc>Fight Night: Round 3 on Xbox is a boxing game that pits you against the world's greatest boxing stars. Various game modes are available (big punch challenge, quick match, ESPN challenge...) and the fights are in 15 rounds. Protect your flanks to win each fight.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fight Night Round 3 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fight Night Round 3 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fight Night Round 3 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15203">
		<path>./Furious Karting (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Furious Karting</name>
		<desc>Furious Karting brings the speed and excitement of kart racing to your neighborhood. Now you can hop into a kart and speed through city streets, shopping malls, and fantasy tracks. During each race, you'll have special moves, pickups, and tricks to help you pass the competition. In addition to battling rival racers in single-player mode, you can compete against your friends in four-player multiplayer mode. No matter which character you play as, you can develop your own racing style and lead your team to victory.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Furious Karting (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Furious Karting (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Furious Karting (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Babylon</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15250">
		<path>./Future Tactics - The Uprising (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Future Tactics : The Uprising</name>
		<desc>Future Tactics: The Uprising is a turn-based strategy game for Xbox. The title invites you to live a futuristic adventure inspired by a very cartoonish universe. The goal is to form a team of mercenaries from a choice of 9 characters with their own characteristics to defeat vile creatures.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Future Tactics - The Uprising (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Future Tactics - The Uprising (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Future Tactics - The Uprising (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040510T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>JoWood Produtions</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15084">
		<path>./Gauntlet - Seven Sorrows (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Gauntlet : Seven Sorrows</name>
		<desc>Gauntlet: Seven Sorrows on Xbox is an action game in which you can choose between four heroes who have been mysteriously freed from a supposedly eternal punishment and are now on a quest for revenge. In their quest, they must face the consequences of their own actions and watch the world break down around them.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet - Seven Sorrows (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet - Seven Sorrows (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet - Seven Sorrows (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14901">
		<path>./Grabbed by the Ghoulies (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Grabbed By The Ghoulies</name>
		<desc>Grabbed by the Ghoulies follows a young man named Cooper Chance who sets out to rescue his girlfriend, Amber, from Ghoulhaven Hall. This mansion is full of supernatural creatures, and Cooper will receive help along the way from the many hired hands that work there.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grabbed by the Ghoulies (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grabbed by the Ghoulies (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grabbed by the Ghoulies (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20031121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Rareware</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14608">
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : San Andreas</name>
		<desc>GTA: San Andreas on Xbox is an action game in which you play as Carl Johnson, a small-time crook who has returned to his hometown. You discover that the hard law of gangs reigns and you have to build a name and reputation to gain respect. The game area is huge and consists of three large cities to complete missions. Murder, corruption, theft, betrayal... Find your place in Los Santos!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Grand Theft Auto</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,es</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14616">
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Vice City</name>
		<desc>In GTA Vice City on Xbox, the player takes on the role of Tommy Vercetti, who must carry out a variety of missions in a city inspired by the Miami of the 1980s. A number of activities are offered alongside the basic missions: taxi driver, fireman, ambulance driver, etc. This action game is based on a gigantic map and an example of non-linearity.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Grand Theft Auto</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14621">
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto III (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto III</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto III is an action game for the Xbox in which you play as a thug who has been betrayed and left for dead. Of course, he wants to take revenge by any means necessary. Break-ins, robberies and score-settling will be your only means of survival in Liberty City, the most decadent city in the USA.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto III (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto III (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto III (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Grand Theft Auto</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15120">
		<path>./Gunmetal.iso</path>
		<name>Gun Metal</name>
		<desc>Gun Metal is a fast-paced, arcade-style action game in which you pilot a mech that can transform into a jet. Use your mech and its advanced weaponry to battle hordes of enemies through 14 different missions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gunmetal.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gunmetal.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gunmetal.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rage Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14620">
		<path>./Half-Life 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Half-life 2</name>
		<desc>Once again players assume the role of Gordon Freeman, a scientist destined to save the Earth from hordes of gruesome alien attackers. Half-Life 2 takes computer games to a new level of realism with incredible in-game graphics that recreate familiar-looking city streets, and blend them with strange and grotesque monsters, resulting in a believable and at times unsettling environment. Objects and characters feature accurate physics properties, behaving with the appropriate mass, density, and physical properties of their real-life counterparts. Extremely intelligent computer AI result in enemies that plan, adapt, and respond to the player's actions.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Half-Life 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Half-Life 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Half-Life 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Half-Life</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15113">
		<path>./Mad Dash Racing (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Mad Dash Racing</name>
		<desc>Mad Dash Racing combines high-speed combat and 3D adventure action with a crew of motley characters for an insane multiplayer competition for up to four. Players select from nine different characters, each with their own unique personality and abilities, and compete in a race for survival against the evil Hex, his dirty minions and your unforgiving friends. Glide across rivers of hot, steaming lava, slip through underwater pipes, bash through mammoth boulders, and slide down icy glaciers to beat the other racers and escape Hex's wicked wrath.



Music by Moby, Fatboy Slim, Propellorheads &amp; More!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mad Dash Racing (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mad Dash Racing (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mad Dash Racing (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15358">
		<path>./Mashed - Fully Loaded (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Mashed Fully Loaded</name>
		<desc>Mashed is an action-packed top-down arcade-racer. On 13 tracks (which must be played free in single-player first) you need all your driving skills to survive and make it to the finish as the 1st with one of the four different cars available (from slow ones to really fast ones).

The heart of the single-player mode (besides the quick battle against the AI) are the bronze, silver and gold challenges for every track you need to complete to play free the next track. Each challenge is one of the seven (eight in multiplayer) game modes available in Mashed. From normal race-events (just be the 1st) over battles where you need to kill all your enemies before they do to the ultimate survival mode where everyone doesn't really like you.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mashed - Fully Loaded (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mashed - Fully Loaded (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mashed - Fully Loaded (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SG Diffusion</developer>
		<publisher>Supersonic Software</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14709">
		<path>./Max Payne (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Max Payne</name>
		<desc>The story is told in medias res and consists of three volumes: "The American Dream", "A Cold Day in Hell", and "A Bit Closer to Heaven". The game begins in the winter of 2001, as New York City finishes experiencing the worst blizzard in the history of the city. The intro sequence shows Max Payne, a renegade DEA agent and former NYPD officer, standing at the top of a skyscraper building as police units arrive. He then experiences a flashback from three years ago. Back in 1998, Max returned home to find that a trio of apparent junkies had broken into his house while high on a new designer drug called Valkyr. Max rushed to the aid his family, but was too late and his wife and their newborn daughter had already been brutally murdered. After his family's funeral, Payne transferred to the DEA. Three years later, Max Payne is employed as an undercover operative inside the Punchinello Mafia family responsible for the trafficking of Valkyr. His DEA colleague B.B. gives Max a message asking him to meet another DEA agent, who is also Max's best friend, Alex Balder, in the NYC Subway station. Max's arrival at the subway results in a shoot-out after he encounters mobsters working for Jack Lupino, a Mafia underboss in the Punchinello crime family, attempting a bank robbery by breaking through from the station. Working his way back to the surface, Max encounters Alex, who is then killed by an unknown assassin and Payne becomes the prime suspect in the murder. Additionally, the Mafia find out that he is a cop and now want him dead.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Max Payne (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Max Payne (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Max Payne (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Remedy</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14698">
		<path>./Max Payne 2 - The Fall of Max Payne (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Max Payne 2 : The Fall of Max Payne</name>
		<desc>A follow-up to 2001's Max Payne, Max Payne 2: The Fall of Max Payne features an all-new intriguing story and more slick combat. You play the role of Payne, a cop caught in a violent, film noir love story with a femme fatale murder suspect. Experience Payne's signature slow-motion gunplay with all new guns and new moves. The game features fully interactive environments, characters with ragdoll physics, and believable enemies. Max Payne 2 sets out to raise the bar for action game intensity once again.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Max Payne 2 - The Fall of Max Payne (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Max Payne 2 - The Fall of Max Payne (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Max Payne 2 - The Fall of Max Payne (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Remedy</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15182">
		<path>./MotoGP (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>MotoGP : Ultimate Racing Technology</name>
		<desc>MotoGP: Ultimate Racing Technology is a motorbike racing game for Xbox. The official championship license allows you to see the real riders in action and relive the 2001 season in its entirety. After beating the competition in single player, take on a friend in split screen.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/MotoGP (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/MotoGP (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/MotoGP (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Motorcycle</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15624">
		<path>./NBA Inside Drive 2002 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Nba Inside Drive 2002</name>
		<desc>NBA Inside Drive 2002 on Xbox is a basketball game that allows you to diversify your involvement. You participate in the game as a player, you trade players as a manager and you can coach by changing your game strategy. Of course, NBA teams are available for Seasons and Exhibition.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NBA Inside Drive 2002 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NBA Inside Drive 2002 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NBA Inside Drive 2002 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20020121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15575">
		<path>./NBA Inside Drive 2004 (USA, Asia).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Nba Inside Drive 2004</name>
		<desc>NBA Inside Drive 2004 est un jeu de basketball sorti sur Xbox. Ce jeu sous licence officielle de la NBA vous propose de jouer avec les vrais sportifs et de disputer le championnat américain officiel.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NBA Inside Drive 2004 (USA, Asia).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NBA Inside Drive 2004 (USA, Asia).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NBA Inside Drive 2004 (USA, Asia).xiso.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20031118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Basketball</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14946">
		<path>./OutRun 2 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>OutRun 2</name>
		<desc>Arcade style racing action meets challenge based skills driving. Driving between different zones to reach the finish point with choices of which route to take along the way means you can select the difficulty along the way. This is the sequel to the original arcade classic and has a very similar style graphically and gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/OutRun 2 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/OutRun 2 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/OutRun 2 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM R&amp;D Dept. #2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>OutRun</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14949">
		<path>./SSX Tricky (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Ssx Tricky</name>
		<desc>Funky riders of all nationalities, stratospheric tricks defying the laws of physics and fierce competitions where hits are more than recommended are on the menu of SSX Tricky, a supercharged snowboarding game on Xbox.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SSX Tricky (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/SSX Tricky (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SSX Tricky (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skiing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15334">
		<path>./UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>UFC Ultimate Fighting Championship : Tapout</name>
		<desc>UFC Tapout is based on the UFC, or the Ultimate Fighting Championship.  The game places you in the position as a real-world fighter, utilizing various fighting styles, such as Freestyle, Wrestling, Kickboxing, Ju Jitsu, etc. Each fighter has a variety of real-life moves, in different categories.  There are punches, kicks, grapples and takedowns.  There are also ways of making your opponent submit, or "tapout", to gain a victory. You have the ability to perform combos, but these combos are realistic; you can perform a 1-2-3-4 punch combo, or a punch-punch-kick, or any variation of those. There are over twenty five fighters in the game, each one based off of real-life UFC fighters.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20020220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Fighting</genre>
		<family>UFC Fighting</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15361">
		<path>./UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout 2 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>UFC Ultimate Fighting Championship : Tapout 2</name>
		<desc>An update from the previous UFC game, Ultimate Fighting Championship: Tapout, this one still features the same type of attacks and combos as it's predecessor.  It features a different publisher than the last one and has  revamped animation models to give it a more life-like feel.  There are 35 real UFC fighters to choose from or players can create their own fighter in the career mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout 2 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout 2 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/UFC - Ultimate Fighting Championship - Tapout 2 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dream Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Fighting</genre>
		<family>UFC Fighting</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14992">
		<path>./Unreal Championship 2 - The Liandri Conflict (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Unreal Championship 2 : The Liandri Conflict</name>
		<desc>Unreal Championship 2: The Liandri Conflict is the sequel to the Xbox Live game Unreal Championship, and was designed from the ground up for Xbox, and the Xbox Live service. The game features 14 different characters and includes an expanded single player mode, enhanced mobility, and expanded upon combo system. The game also adds melee combat, by giving each character the possibility to switch to their respective weapon (e.g. blade, staff).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unreal Championship 2 - The Liandri Conflict (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Unreal Championship 2 - The Liandri Conflict (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unreal Championship 2 - The Liandri Conflict (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15057">
		<path>./Unreal II - The Awakening (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Unreal II : The Awakening</name>
		<desc>The player controls a former Marine John Dalton, a Terran Colonial Authority Marshal whose job is to patrol remote areas of space far away from any real action. He is called back into service to retrieve seven pieces of an ancient artifact thought to make a powerful weapon when assembled.



The plot follows a pre-set linear path like many first-person shooters, with the character going to various planets in search of the artifacts. Level design at each location is also linear, with a certain amount of puzzle solving and key finding.



Environments on each planet are quite diverse, ranging from tropical to desert, bunkers and industrial installations, and alien cities and even inside the bodies of aliens. During several missions the player must hold a location against waves of incoming enemies, in some cases using NPCs and equipment (such as sentry guns) as support.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unreal II - The Awakening (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Unreal II - The Awakening (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unreal II - The Awakening (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137540">
		<path>./Volvo - Drive for Life (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Volvo : Drive For Life</name>
		<desc>Volvo: Drive For Life lets players test drive the S40, S60R, and XC90 V8. First each car must be driven on a special test track that demonstrates a unique safety/control feature of each vehicle. Afterwards each car can be modified with a paint job, rims, and interior package and driven on a special track: a highway that winds along the beach and cliffs for the S40, a snowy mountain pass for the XC90 V8, and a race circuit for the S60R. Also included are crash test videos and promotional videos for each of the three cars.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Volvo - Drive for Life (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Volvo - Drive for Life (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Volvo - Drive for Life (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20050818T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Action</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15360">
		<path>./Warpath.iso</path>
		<name>WarPath</name>
		<desc>Warpath is a budget-priced first-person shooter from the same people that developed Pariah. As such, the gameplay is very similar to that game. For instance, you can heal yourself with a portable healing tool, and run at speeds so fast that they blur your vision. The main difference between the two games is that the singleplayer game is multiplayer-oriented, similar to Unreal Tournament. There is a storyline, however. You can select from one of three races fighting for the control of a beautiful, resource-rich planet named Kaladi. The Ohm are a cyborg-like race that need the planet's resources to live. The House of Kovos are robots that want to take control of Kaladi because their religion says that they should. The Human Coalition is a group of homeless humans that are trying to find a home.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Warpath.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Warpath.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Warpath.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Extremes</developer>
		<publisher>Groove Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>1-16</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="15028">
		<path>./World Racing 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>World Racing 2</name>
		<desc>Compared to its predecessor, where players could only drive different Mercedes Benz cars, this sequel allows them to control over 90 different cars from 17 different manufacturers, such as Alfa Romeo, Morgan, and others. The core of the game is the career-mode with 120 races which take players all around the globe, from Italy to Florida, where players can earn their 'Speedbucks' to buy new cars and tuning options. The game also features oncoming traffic and a detailed damage model including realistic driving physics. Players can also customize their cars with vinyls, alloy rims and many other extras.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/World Racing 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/World Racing 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/World Racing 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20051125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Synetic</developer>
		<publisher>Playlogic</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137536">
		<path>./World Series Baseball (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>World Series Baseball</name>
		<desc>World Series Baseball makes its appearance for the 2003 season. This installment includes an in-depth franchise mode that allows players to manage their coaches and minor league teams, playing it for an unlimited number of seasons.  In what has since almost become a standard for the series, Create-a-Player mode is present for players to make their own teams. Also featured are Season, Exhibition, Home Run Derby and Playoffs modes.  Little extras include saving the player's statistics to a user profile, and old-school players and uniforms. The game utilizes licenses from the MLBA, the MLB Players Choice, the National Baseball Hall of Fame, the Cooperstown Collection, and the 2002 World Series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/World Series Baseball (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/World Series Baseball (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/World Series Baseball (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20020519T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>World Series Baseball</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137539">
		<path>./World War II Combat - Iwo Jima (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>World War II Combat : Iwo Jima</name>
		<desc>World War II Combat: Iwo Jima is a follow-up to World War II Combat: Road to Berlin, sporting the same gameplay mechanics and budget price tag of its predecessor. The gameplay is basically just like any other first-person shooter out there, but you can't pick up any weapons or health during a mission -- instead, your health recharges at the end of each mission and your weapons are automatically assigned for each mission. The main difference between Road to Berlin and Iwo Jima is that you're now pitted against the Japanese instead of the Germans, as the only surviving member of a squad of Marines during the American conquest of the Japanese island Iwo Jima.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/World War II Combat - Iwo Jima (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/World War II Combat - Iwo Jima (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/World War II Combat - Iwo Jima (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>20060721T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Direct Action Games</developer>
		<publisher>Groove Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14767">
		<path>./Worms 4 - Mayhem (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Worms 4 : Mayhem</name>
		<desc>Worms 4: Mayhem is a sequel to Worms 3D. Like its predecessor, it is a turn-based artillery variant with humorous themes and weapons, in which players control small armies of worms. The gameplay is similar to that of the previous game, adding a more developed Story mode, in which the player cooperates with the wise Professor Worminkle, who can use a time machine to travel to different time periods such as American Old West, ancient Arabia, and Prehistoric Age. In this installment, players can customize the appearance of their worms, including helmets, glasses, facial hair, gloves, etc. A new mode called "Weapon Factory" has been added, allowing players to forge their own weapons. The game also contains a shop where players can purchase various items, using points accumulated by completing story missions or unlocking trophies. Shop items include new maps, accessories, outfits, character voices, etc.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Worms 4 - Mayhem (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Worms 4 - Mayhem (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Worms 4 - Mayhem (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Worms</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14918">
		<path>./WWE Raw 2 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>WWE Raw 2</name>
		<desc>WWE Raw 2 is a follow-up to WWF Raw. The game contains new modes, superstars, and an enhanced season mode. It features 64 WWE superstars, along with the ability to add 64 additional wrestlers of the player's own creation from the Create-a-Superstar mode. New modes include Ladder Matches, Table Matches, Cage Matches, and "Hell in a Cell." All of these modes can be played with up to five other CPU-controlled wrestlers (or three other human opponents). The season mode allows the player to choose any superstar, be it a WWE star or a wrestler he has created, and play his way through a year's worth of WWE programming. Set traps, interfere with other matches, steal from other wrestlers, and encourage others in order to make it all the way to Wrestlemania.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/WWE Raw 2 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/WWE Raw 2 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/WWE Raw 2 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anchor</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15073">
		<path>./Advent Rising.iso</path>
		<name>Advent Rising</name>
		<desc>Advent Rising is a sci-fi shooter with a storyline penned by author Orson Scott Card, whose video game credits include The Dig and the Monkey Island series of adventure games. Advent Rising tells the story of a supposedly peaceful race called the Seekers. The setting takes place in a universe where planets have banded together to shape future policy and promote goodwill throughout the galaxy. It is a universe where members of an intergalactic council have appointed the Seekers as overseers in the development of new civilizations before these planets are permitted to join the esteemed council. Yet the Seekers are not as diplomatic as they seem. Another species has learned of a sinister plot by the Seekers to eliminate the human race.

 



A small band of human freedom fighters, led by a man named Gideon Wyeth, plans to stop this form of genocide at all costs. Players assume the role of Gideon while exploring the 3D worlds from a third-person perspective. Advent Rising offers a variety of weapons with which to thwart the armies of Seekers, and players will also be able to commandeer vehicles and channel special mind powers for protection as well as offense. The first of a planned trilogy of titles, Advent Rising uses Epic Games' Unreal technology to create the worlds in which players must battle. Orson Scott Card has also written a companion novel to expand upon the ideas found in the game, which can be purchased at the time of Advent Rising's release.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Advent Rising.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Advent Rising.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Advent Rising.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Glyphx</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="204082">
		<path>./Big Bumpin' (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Big Bumpin'</name>
		<desc>Big Bumpin' looks like a traditional carnival bumper car ride and features familiar BURGER KING icons, including the Subservient Chicken and Brooke Burke. But, there's a catch – Big Bumpin' arenas come with some big hazards, like surprise saws, bottomless pits and "power up" items that let gamers dole out thundering bumps. With several different types of game play, gamers have a chance to hone their bumper car skills in a variety of challenging scenarios. The game features theme parks, including the "Ice Box," "Broiler," "King's Court," "The Deep" and "Monsoon of Doom," and three modes of play for each – intense four-player and XBOX Live-supported. Easy to learn. Fun to play. Difficult to avoid a major crash.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Big Bumpin' (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Big Bumpin' (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Big Bumpin' (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>King Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15298">
		<path>./Black Stone - Magic &amp; Steel (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Blackstone : Magic &amp; Steel</name>
		<desc>The protectors of good are ready to destroy all that is evil! Battle against the Dark Lord in an effort to save the world of Zedan. With 20 different characters, 26 levels, four-player gameplay, and non-stop, hack-and-slash action.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Black Stone - Magic &amp; Steel (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Black Stone - Magic &amp; Steel (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Black Stone - Magic &amp; Steel (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20030321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xicat Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14989">
		<path>./Blinx 2 - Masters of Time &amp; Space (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Blinx 2 : Masters of Time &amp; Space</name>
		<desc>Blinx 2: Masters of Time and Space is a race up against the Tom Tom Gang for the pieces of the Big Crystal. The game is different than the first as players take control of the Time Sweepers and mastering time. The Tom Tom Gang control space. However, the player does not play as Blinx. The time limit is also gone from each level. The game is more of an action game rather than a platform game. Artoon's game has expanded into non-traditional platform territories and plays more like a light-weight action game. The player has a huge arsenal of gadgets and weapons. The switch between the two teams is a new experience.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blinx 2 - Masters of Time &amp; Space (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blinx 2 - Masters of Time &amp; Space (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blinx 2 - Masters of Time &amp; Space (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,jp,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14866">
		<path>./American McGee Presents Scrapland (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Scrapland</name>
		<desc>Scrapland on Xbox is a decidedly robotic action/adventure game. D-tritus is a friendly space adventurer who decides to land on the planet Scrapland, populated only by artificial beings. Soon, his job as a press photographer leads him into a dark story of murder.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/American McGee Presents Scrapland (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/American McGee Presents Scrapland (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/American McGee Presents Scrapland (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>MercurySteam Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Enlight Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137569">
		<path>./Championship Manager - Season 02-03 (Europe) (En,De,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Championship Manager : Season 02/03</name>
		<desc>Championship Manager 3 is now exclusive on the Xbox in this iteration. Covering seasons 2002-2003 with: Up to date team and player data for over 100,000 footballers and staff. Managing any team from 27 worldwide leagues. Includes the updated FIFA transfer system.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Championship Manager - Season 02-03 (Europe) (En,De,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Championship Manager - Season 02-03 (Europe) (En,De,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Championship Manager - Season 02-03 (Europe) (En,De,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20021206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sports Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14753">
		<path>./Fatal Frame (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Project Zero</name>
		<desc>Project Zero is a survival-horror released on Xbox. Guide Miku, a young girl in search of her brother, as she investigates the murky past of the Himuro Mansion. Armed with her sixth sense and a simple camera, young Miku is about to experience a terrifying adventure...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fatal Frame (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fatal Frame (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fatal Frame (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15465">
		<path>./Iron Phoenix (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Iron Phoenix</name>
		<desc>Iron Phoenix is a Wuxia/Hong Kong Cinema style fighting game that allows Xbox Live battles with up to 16 players. The fighting system is based on the weapon and character selection, allowing hundreds of move combinations. In the distant past, a meteorite fell to earth (the "Iron Phoenix") and was forged into seven powerful magical weapons by a master weaponsmith. They proved to be his doom, however, as the World of Martial Arts is nothing if not unkind to those without the power to protect what is theirs.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Iron Phoenix (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Iron Phoenix (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Iron Phoenix (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>InterServ</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>16</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15442">
		<path>./Jacked.iso</path>
		<name>Jacked</name>
		<desc>Reminiscent of the classic Road Rash, Jacked is a high-octane arcade motorcycle racer featuring over-the-top combat elements. In Jacked, the world's fastest and hottest motorbikes - including the gas turbine powered Marine Turbine Superbike - can be yours. Race across the USA, from New York to LA, fulfill a variety of missions and steal your enemies' bikes at high speed while they are moving by "jacking" them. Fight your enemies with baseball bats and tazers, flame them with Molotov Cocktails, shoot them off their rides with shotguns or blow them out of the way with frag grenades. When they are stunned you can jack their bikes - at any speed, on the road or in midair. In some missions you can even take your biker gang along to help you out in your endeavors.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jacked.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jacked.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jacked.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sproing</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14944">
		<path>./Magic - The Gathering - Battlegrounds (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Magic : The Gathering : Battlegrounds</name>
		<desc>Magic: The Gathering - Battlegrounds is a real-time fighting/strategy game in which players use Magic: The Gathering cards to combat each other. Three possible types of spells can be played: creatures, sorceries and enchantments.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Magic - The Gathering - Battlegrounds (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Magic - The Gathering - Battlegrounds (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Magic - The Gathering - Battlegrounds (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Secret Level</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14759">
		<path>./Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Marvel Ultimate Alliance</name>
		<desc>When Doctor Doom assaults the SHIELD Helicarrier, an emergency call is sent to all available heroes. Why Doom would choose to make such a direct attack and draw the attention of the world's mightiest heroes is curious, but there's no time to contemplate the reasoning behind the attack. You must first punch things and make them explode. Questions can be asked later.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Marvel</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14839">
		<path>./MechAssault.iso</path>
		<name>Mechassault</name>
		<desc>MechAssault was the first BattleMech video game published for the Xbox. Developed by Day 1 Studios and published by Microsoft, MechAssault was initiated when Denny Thorley of Day 1 Studios approached Jon Kimmich of Microsoft about developing an original BattleTech game built from the ground up to support console play.[1] "MechAssault" was released in November of 2002. A sequel, MechAssault 2: Lone Wolf, was released on December 28, 2004. Both games are set in the BattleTech fictional universe</desc>
		<image>./mixart/MechAssault.png</image>
		<video>./snap/MechAssault.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/MechAssault.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Day 1 Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14741">
		<path>./Mercenaries (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Mercenaries</name>
		<desc>Anything goes in this Playground of Destruction. You are a lethal Mercenary. Your mission is to topple a sinister military regime by any means necessary. If it drives or flies, you can hijack it. If it shoots or explodes, you can use it as a weapon. You are free to go anywhere, destroy anything and blow the crap out of everything. In this playground of destruction, there are no limits, no barriers and no mercy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mercenaries (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mercenaries (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mercenaries (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic Studios</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15241">
		<path>./Metal Dungeon (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Metal Dungeon</name>
		<desc>In the battle for world domination, the leaders of Giamel have begun producing Weapon Monsters, horrible biomechanical killing machines. The only ones with the power to produce such beings are the Gods of Magic, a group of sorcerers who have been captured and put into a trance so that their powers can be harvested for this end. However, the have started to awaken and now they are using these Weapon Monsters to wreak vengeance on those who kidnapped them. Their ultimate goal is the total destruction of the earth. You and your band of mercenaries are the only ones who can stop them.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Dungeon (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Dungeon (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Dungeon (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20021206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Panther Software</developer>
		<publisher>Xicat Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14625">
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid 2 - Substance (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid 2 Substance</name>
		<desc>Metal Gear Solid 2: Substance is a re-vamped and revised edition of the original Metal Gear Solid 2: Sons of Liberty, in which Solid Snake must recover the stolen Metal Gear Ray from a group of terrorists bent on using its power for unthinkable reasons.

Along with the original espionage shooter comes a collection of 200 virtual reality (VR) missions. Missions range from killing certain targets and using particular weapons, as well as seeing the world of Solid Snake from different perspectives and styles, with first-person target modes and a variety mode including crazy characters of different shapes and sizes.

Also included are various alternative missions, ranging from the protagonist sneaking around and snapping photos of targets to bomb disposal, all out destruction, and more.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Gear Solid 2 - Substance (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear Solid 2 - Substance (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Gear Solid 2 - Substance (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Metal Gear</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14851">
		<path>./Myst IV - Revelation (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Myst IV : Revelation</name>
		<desc>Myst IV: Revelation on Xbox is an adventure/thought game that takes you to the side of Atrus. This descendant of the D'ni people has locked his sons in ages, after they oppressed the people with an infamous dictatorship. It is now up to you to determine if these offspring are worthy of their father's forgiveness, by traversing ages filled with many riddles.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Myst IV - Revelation (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Myst IV - Revelation (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Myst IV - Revelation (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15151">
		<path>./Namco Museum 50th Anniversary (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Namco Museum 50th Anniversary</name>
		<desc>Namco Museum 50th Anniversary on Xbox is a compilation that gathers, on the occasion of Namco's 50th anniversary, 14 of the titles that made the great days of the editor. Pac-Man, Ms. Pac-Man, Galaga, Galaxian, Dig Dug, Pole Position, Pole Position II, Rolling Thunder, Rally X, Bosconian, Dragon Spirit, Sky Kid, Xevious and Mappy are all in one box.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Namco Museum 50th Anniversary (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Namco Museum 50th Anniversary (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Namco Museum 50th Anniversary (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Inside Drive 2003 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>NBA Inside Drive 2003</name>
		<desc>Inside Drive is solid on almost every front except for some aspects of the offensive game, the most notable problem being the inability to pass out of layups or similar moves to the basket. One of the most important aspects of professional basketball is being able to drive to the lane and have a player make it look like he's going up for a shot so that he can draw defense, but then pass the ball to an open man on the inside or to a wide-open player out on the perimeter. Indeed, generally driving through the lane can be a little problematic since the AI tends to latch onto players in the paint, and the juke moves can be difficult to use effectively against tough opponents.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NBA Inside Drive 2003 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NBA Inside Drive 2003 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NBA Inside Drive 2003 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15603">
		<path>./NFL Fever 2002 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Nfl Fever 2002</name>
		<desc>NFL Fever 2002 is an American football game for Xbox. Play with the 31 NFL teams of the year 2001. Try to reach the Super Bowl by any means possible. Play a full season with your favourite team. As you progress, the players' stats change. Create your dream team by drafting your favorite players in Dynasty mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NFL Fever 2002 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NFL Fever 2002 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NFL Fever 2002 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL Fever 2003 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>NFL Fever 2003</name>
		<desc>NFL Fever 2003 is an American football video game published and developed by Microsoft Game Studios. It was originally released on August 6, 2002 for the Xbox video game console. The game, which was also used for beta testing for Xbox Live, was preceded by NFL Fever 2002 and followed by NFL Fever 2004.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NFL Fever 2003 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/NFL Fever 2003 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NFL Fever 2003 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14623">
		<path>./Oddworld - Stranger's Wrath (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Oddworld : Stranger's Wrath</name>
		<desc>A bounty hunter known only as the Stranger is pursuing and capturing various criminals, trying to earn enough money for a mysterious operation. When he hears that a town populated by Grubbs has been invaded by a demon, the Stranger ventures there. The town was once protected by a race of creatures known as the Steef, who now appear to be completely extinct. The Stranger soon discovers that a nearby river has been dried up by a dam, built by a person called Sekto. The Stranger must confront this person as he continues to hunt down outlaws, revealing nothing about his past. Oddworld: Stranger's Wrath is set in the fictional Oddworld universe, differing in many ways from the preceding installment. The game incorporates two basic genres: third-person platforming action and first-person shooter. The player can switch between the modes at any time by using a melee or a ranged weapon, respectively. The goal of the game, for the most part, is to bag the outlaws and bring them in, collecting "moolah" (the game's currency) in the process. The Stranger can stun or knock down enemies, as well as use a stealthy approach, e.g. hiding in long grass to surprise the enemy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Oddworld - Stranger's Wrath (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Oddworld - Stranger's Wrath (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Oddworld - Stranger's Wrath (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137516">
		<path>./Outlaw Golf - Holiday Golf (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Outlaw Golf : 9 Holes Of X-Mas</name>
		<desc>It's the holidays and here are 9 all-new holes for the holidays. A small taste of Outlaw Golf but on slippery slopes, frozen greens, and other cold wintery conditions to challenge you on these courses.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Outlaw Golf - Holiday Golf (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Outlaw Golf - Holiday Golf (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outlaw Golf - Holiday Golf (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20021213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hypnotix</developer>
		<publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<family>Outlaw Golf</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="204038">
		<path>./Outlaw Volleyball - Red Hot (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Outlaw Volleyball : Red Hot</name>
		<desc>A Blockbuster Video Exclusive game for the 2003 Halloween season. This acts like a demo for those not familiar with Outlaw Volleyball and has some new features for those who are. Some of the new items: Halloween costumes for many of the female characters and a new court.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Outlaw Volleyball - Red Hot (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Outlaw Volleyball - Red Hot (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outlaw Volleyball - Red Hot (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20031001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hypnotix</developer>
		<publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Volleyball</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14984">
		<path>./Pariah (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Pariah</name>
		<desc>Pariah on Xbox is a first-person shooter set on Earth in 2520. In charge of escorting a strange prisoner suffering from a no less strange virus, you quickly realise that the girl has gone rogue. It's up to you to find her, knowing that the fate of humanity on the blue planet depends on this mission.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pariah (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pariah (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pariah (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hip Games</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Extremes</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-16</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15275">
		<path>./Phantom Crash (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Phantom Crash</name>
		<desc>In the wake of massive air pollution and economic disaster in Tokyo, Japan has relocated its capital. Old Tokyo has become the battleground for a new breed of public entertainment called Rumbling. Observing from a massive airborne viewing station, spectators watch Scoobees battle to the death. More than just high-speed, heavily armed Mechs, Scoobees have an unprecedented stealth capability, turning invisible at will for brief periods of time. The stakes are high. The enemies are ruthless. The action is intense. Are you ready to rumble.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Phantom Crash (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Phantom Crash (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Phantom Crash (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Phantagram Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Genki</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15314">
		<path>./Pilot Down - Behind Enemy Lines.iso</path>
		<name>Pilot Down : Derrière les Lignes Ennemies</name>
		<desc>Pilot Down: Behind Enemy Lines is an infiltration game set during World War II. You are an American pilot whose plane has been shot down. Your goal is simple, to get to Switzerland. A survival bar, directly affecting your health, is to be watched closely, symbolizing your hunger and fatigue. Because it is well known that the German winter is very harsh.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pilot Down - Behind Enemy Lines.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pilot Down - Behind Enemy Lines.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pilot Down - Behind Enemy Lines.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxygen Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Kuju Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="204034">
		<path>./PocketBike Racer (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>PocketBike Racer</name>
		<image>./mixart/PocketBike Racer (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/PocketBike Racer (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/PocketBike Racer (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20061119T000000</releasedate>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15347">
		<path>./Psyvariar 2 - Extend Edition (Japan).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Psyvariar 2</name>
		<desc>Psyvariar 2 is a shooting game available on Xbox. This game uses a particular system called the buzz. When you come close to an enemy shot, this gauge increases to level up your robot. The player can choose between 2 robots: Yuhei puts a lot of emphasis on the buzz, while Kei makes your bar increase faster by shooting.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Psyvariar 2 - Extend Edition (Japan).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Psyvariar 2 - Extend Edition (Japan).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Psyvariar 2 - Extend Edition (Japan).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20041028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skonec</developer>
		<publisher>Success</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="153060">
		<path>./Pulse Racer (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Pulse Racer</name>
		<desc>Pulse Racer is a racing game set in 2024 in futuristic vehicles that resemble karts. They have weaponry power-ups, where the car is linked directly to the driver, allowing the player to speed up at the cost of the character's heart rate and to race on life energy instead of fuel. Included are quick race, time trial, career, and multiplayer modes. Also of interest is the INFINITRAX system, which generates custom tracks that can be saved on the hard disk. While progressing through the game the game, more and more sliders are unlocked, allowing heavier customization of the maps.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pulse Racer (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pulse Racer (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pulse Racer (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20030102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15253">
		<path>./Raze's Hell (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Raze's Hell</name>
		<desc>Raze's Hell is a unique take on good vs. evil as the player takes control of a monster named Raze as he travels through 20 different lands to free his planet from the cute and cuddly Kewletts.  The Kewletts and their leader, the Twisted Princess, is bent on turning the planet and its inhabitants into them at all costs and it's up to Raze to stop them.



The gameplay mostly consists of traveling around while destroying enemies with weapons such as grenades, sniper rifles and even acid projectiles that Raze spits out of his mouth.  The player must also watch out for the Kewletts weaponry which consists of bunny rocket launchers, lollipop axes and even exploding jack in the boxes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Raze's Hell (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Raze's Hell (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Raze's Hell (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artech Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14776">
		<path>./Red Dead Revolver (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Red Dead Revolver</name>
		<desc>Orphaned by bandits and left for dead on the frontier, Red Harlow grew up with a scar burned into his hand and the lust for revenge burned into his heart.  Surviving as a bounty hunter in the rough-and-tumble Old West, Red stays ever watchful for some clue that could lead him to the men who murdered his father and mother -- and then one day, that clue appears. Step into Red's spurred boots, and take up his mission of revenge.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Red Dead Revolver (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Red Dead Revolver (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Red Dead Revolver (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14836">
		<path>./Return to Castle Wolfenstein - Tides of War (World).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Return to Castle Wolfenstein : Tides of War</name>
		<desc>Return to Castle Wolfenstein: Tides of War is an updated re-release for the Xbox based on the original PC version Return to Castle Wolfenstein. Next to the full, original singleplayer campaign, there are 7 new prologue levels that show how B.J. and Agent One first met and how they got captured and imprisoned at Wolfenstein Castle. There is also a secret bonus awarded at the end of every level when every secret area has been found.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Return to Castle Wolfenstein - Tides of War (World).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Return to Castle Wolfenstein - Tides of War (World).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Return to Castle Wolfenstein - Tides of War (World).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-16</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>wr</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15384">
		<path>./Robot Wars - Extreme Destruction.iso</path>
		<name>Robot Wars Extreme Destruction</name>
		<desc>A sequel to BBC Multimedia's first Robot Wars game, Robot Wars: Arenas of Destruction.

This game is based on the TV show Robot Wars. In the game you get to create your own robot, or use robots from the TV show, and battle your way through all the competitions.

The sequel brings you 8 new and improved arenas, new weapons, all new robots, and a much improved robot creator.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Robot Wars - Extreme Destruction.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Robot Wars - Extreme Destruction.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robot Wars - Extreme Destruction.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>BBC Multimedia</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="14732">
		<path>./RollerCoaster Tycoon (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Rollercoaster Tycoon</name>
		<image>./mixart/RollerCoaster Tycoon (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/RollerCoaster Tycoon (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/RollerCoaster Tycoon (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20030325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chris Sawyer</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15255">
		<path>./Sea Blade.iso</path>
		<name>Seablade</name>
		<desc>Search, Rescue, and Destroy in the air and under the sea. White-knuckle fly-and-shoot action! 39 adrenaline-pumping missions. Advanced weaponry for maximum firepower. 6 challenging apocalyptic environments. Unlock SeaBlades for Multiplay: 2-4 players.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sea Blade.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sea Blade.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sea Blade.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TDK</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="204024">
		<path>./Sneak King (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Sneak King</name>
		<image>./mixart/Sneak King (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sneak King (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sneak King (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20061119T000000</releasedate>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14704">
		<path>./Soldier of Fortune II - Double Helix (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Soldier of Fortune II : Double Helix</name>
		<desc>Soldier of Fortune 2: Double Helix is a first-person shooter for Xbox in which a terrorist organisation threatens to decimate the world with a double virus called Gemini. The player takes on the role of John Mullins, the only one who can stop the terrorists before it's too late. Frontal attacks, stealth and cunning will be your trump cards.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Soldier of Fortune II - Double Helix (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soldier of Fortune II - Double Helix (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soldier of Fortune II - Double Helix (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-12</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Spikeout: Battle Street</name>
		<desc>Based on the 3D coin-on arcade title of the same name, SpikeOut: Battle Street offers a quick single-player mode that's about two to four hours long and each time it's beaten, a new character, with slightly different special attacks, opens up. There are around 10 levels, and 12 unlockable characters, and an online mode. You can connect with three other players for a four-player online bout on Xbox Live, and as a "sort-of" team, you then proceed to smack infinite nameless thugs into polygonal paste. The game works one way: Four humans against the computer AI. You've got a punch, kick, jump, and grapple move, and when pressed multiple times, each button ignites combos. By grappling an enemy from various angles and by pressing the Dpad in different directions when executing the throw renders various satisfying hurls.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spikeout - Battle Street (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>de,en,jp,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14718">
		<path>./Star Wars - Battlefront (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars Battlefront</name>
		<desc>Star Wars Battlefront is an action game available on Xbox. Play as a soldier and fight on all fronts using all the weapons and vehicles at your disposal (TB-TT, X-Wing, speeder...). You can of course choose your side and your character class to take part in a host of missions alone or in multiplayer. Up to 32 players can compete in a network.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Battlefront (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Battlefront (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Battlefront (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<family>Star Wars</family>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (En,Es,It) (Rev 1).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Battlefront II</name>
		<desc>Battlefront II features a more narrative-based campaign, retelling portions of the Star Wars story from the point of view of a veteran Imperial stormtrooper, reminiscing about his tour of duty in service of both the Galactic Republic and as part of the Galactic Empire. Gameplay additions over Battlefront include the use of Jedi, additional game modes, and objective-based space battles.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (En,Es,It) (Rev 1).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (En,Es,It) (Rev 1).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (En,Es,It) (Rev 1).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic Studios</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>32</players>
		<lang>en,es,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14613">
		<path>./Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Knights of the Old Republic</name>
		<desc>Long before the Galactic Civil War, an epic drama begins. Engage in this saga set in the Golden Age of the Republic--over 4,000 years before the first Star Wars film, when both Jedi and Sith number in the thousands. With the Galaxy reeling from a recent conflict with the Dark Lords, the ongoing battle between the Jedi and the Sith rages on. It's up to guide your customizable and evolving characters through ten different worlds, fast-paced minigames, and locations including a Sith world, the Wookie homeworld, and the Jedi Academy. Your actions determine the outcome of this colossal galactic war--and your destiny as a Jedi.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic (USA) (Rev 1).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20030715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>BioWare</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Star Wars</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic II - The Sith Lords (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic II - The Sith Lords</name>
		<desc>The game takes place five years after the events of Knights of the Old Republic, in a time when the Jedi have been nearly exterminated by the Sith. The player's character, a former Jedi Knight exiled from the Jedi Order, is referred to as "The Exile" or "Jedi Exile." Throughout the game, the player's character (canonically a female, although the player can choose to play either sex) restores their connection to the Force while, with the help of non-player character companions, trying to stop the Sith. The player makes choices that turn the Exile to either the light side or the dark side of the Force, and travels to six planets to either help or hinder the Republic's efforts to bring peace and stability to the galaxy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic II - The Sith Lords (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic II - The Sith Lords (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Knights of the Old Republic II - The Sith Lords (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Obsidian Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14766">
		<path>./Still Life (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Still Life</name>
		<desc>In Still Life, you play the role of Victoria McPherson, a young FBI agent who's investigating a serial murder case. Set in modern Chicago and late-1920s Prague, the game lets you investigate the crime scenes of gruesome serial homicides. With the body count now at five, you must solve puzzles, interact with characters, and gather clues to stop the killer from striking again. You'll soon find that, oddly enough, Victoria's present case resembles the one from the past, right down to the killer's MO.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Still Life (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Still Life (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Still Life (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MC2 France</developer>
		<publisher>MC2 France</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14939">
		<path>./Stubbs the Zombie in Rebel Without a Pulse (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Stubbs The Zombie In Rebel Without A Pulse</name>
		<desc>Set in a retro future as depicted in the 1950's, you take on the role of the likeable and eccentric Zombie, Stubbs as he tries to reunite with his lost love.

 

Well that, and seek revenge on the town that awoke him by turning them all into an army of the undead.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Stubbs the Zombie in Rebel Without a Pulse (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Stubbs the Zombie in Rebel Without a Pulse (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Stubbs the Zombie in Rebel Without a Pulse (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>Wideload</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15480">
		<path>./Super Bubble Pop (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Super Bubble Pop</name>
		<desc>Super Bubble Pop is a video game of the puzzle genre released in 2002 by Runecraft. The Player is able to choose from 5 DJ poppers, including 2 unlockable ones, along with 4 grooving soundtracks. They are faced with rows of advancing bubbles of different colors. They can launch bubbles of their own. The idea is to create a row, column or stack of 3 or more bubbles. When that happens, they will pop. Each character has their own favorite bubble color and when they pop them, color energy is transferred to their special jar. Once the jar is full, the player can unleash their super special attack. During the puzzles, the player is also provided with nine different special attacks that they can obtain by getting special bubbles.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Bubble Pop (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Bubble Pop (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Bubble Pop (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20021225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15032">
		<path>./Taito Legends (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Taito Legends</name>
		<desc>The complete Taito Legends title list: Space Invaders (1978), Phoenix(1980), Space Invaders Part 2 (1980), Colony 7 (1981), Electric Yoyo (1982), Jungle Hunt (1982), Zoo Keeper (1982), Elevator Action (1983), Great Swordsman (1984), Return of the Invaders (1985), Bubble Bobble (1986), Gladiator (1986), Tokio (1986), Exzisus (1987), Plump Pop (1987), Operation Wolf (1987), Rainbow Islands (1987), Rastan (1987), Super Qix (1987), The New Zealand Story (1988), Operation Thunderbolt (1988), Battle Shark (1989), Continental Circus (1989), Plotting (1989), Volfied (1989), Ninja Kids (1990), Space Gun (1990), Thunderfox (1990) Tube It (1993).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Taito Legends (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Taito Legends (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Taito Legends (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15289">
		<path>./Taito Legends 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Taito Legends 2</name>
		<desc>Taito Legends 2 on Xbox brings together 40 hits from the famous video game brand: Lunar Rescue, Alpine Ski, The Fairyland Story, KiKi KaiKai, Kuri Kinton, Syvalion, BonzeAdventure, Cameltry, Don Doko Don, Super Space Invaders 91, Growl, PuLiRuLa , Metal Black, Grid Seeker, Space Invaders DX, Darius Gaiden, Dungeon Magic, Elevator Action Returns, Cleopatra Fortune, Puchi Carat, Crazy Balloon, Balloon Bomber, Qix, Wild Western, Chack'n Pop, Frontline, Legend of Kage, Rastan 2 and many more...nn</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Taito Legends 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Taito Legends 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Taito Legends 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KOCH Media</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15212">
		<path>./Tecmo Classic Arcade (USA, Japan).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Tecmo Classic Arcade</name>
		<desc>Tecmo Classic Arcade on Xbox is a compilation of the company's historical hits. On the menu: sports (Swimmer, Tecmo cup), shooters (Pleiads), puzzle/action (Bomb-Jack) or even pinball, there is something for everyone! Eleven games in total dating from the glorious era of the 80s.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tecmo Classic Arcade (USA, Japan).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tecmo Classic Arcade (USA, Japan).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tecmo Classic Arcade (USA, Japan).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20051027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14878">
		<path>./Tenchu - Return from Darkness (USA, Asia).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Tenchu : Return From Darkness</name>
		<desc>Tenchu: Return of the Darkness is an infiltration game for Xbox. The story takes place in 16th century Japan where violent revolts and a civil war break out. You play as a ninja under the orders of Lord Gohda who charges you with stopping Tenrai. The game includes 11 levels and over 20 ninja weapons and equipment.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tenchu - Return from Darkness (USA, Asia).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tenchu - Return from Darkness (USA, Asia).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tenchu - Return from Darkness (USA, Asia).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14794">
		<path>./Thief - Deadly Shadows (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Thief: Deadly Shadows</name>
		<desc>Master Thief Garrett is contacted by the Keeper Artemus, who wants him to steal two valuable artifacts. Meanwhile, Garrett learns that the coming of a Dark Age had been prophesied long ago. Gaining access to the Keeper Prophecies, Garrett learns that an ancient book known as the Compendium of Reproach contains more information about the prophecy. As Garrett is trying to solve the mystery, it becomes more and more clear to him that there is a traitor in the order of the Keepers.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Thief - Deadly Shadows (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Thief - Deadly Shadows (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Thief - Deadly Shadows (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ion Storm</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14692">
		<path>./TimeSplitters - Future Perfect (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>TimeSplitters : Future Perfect</name>
		<desc>The game's story finds Cortez, the series' hero, on a quest to discover the origins of the TimeSplitters, an enigmatic group that travels through time causing trouble for the good people of Earth. Using the paradoxes of time travel to his advantage, the hero can regularly join up with past and future versions of himself, to fight the enemy as a team. A wide selection of historical, modern, and futuristic weapons is available, and environments feature destructible elements.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TimeSplitters - Future Perfect (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TimeSplitters - Future Perfect (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TimeSplitters - Future Perfect (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14647">
		<path>./TimeSplitters 2 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Timesplitters 2</name>
		<desc>The evil race of TimeSplitters is traveling back into human history authoring events that are leading to the enslavement of mankind. In control of a motley crew of renegade characters, you must hunt down the TimeSplitters in historical eras like the gangster-ridden 1920s, the lush jungles of Aztec temples, soviet military installations of the Cold War, and futuristic robot factories in space. To end their evil plot, seek and recover the crystals required to seal the rift in time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TimeSplitters 2 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TimeSplitters 2 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TimeSplitters 2 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Software</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>24</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14835">
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Ghost Recon 2</name>
		<desc>Ghost Recon 2 is a first-person tactical shooter for Xbox. Command your team and represent the elite international forces in the chaos of tomorrow's war. Your ability to use the weapons technologies of the future will be critical to your control of the battlefield.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Storm Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon</family>
		<players>2-16</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15059">
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 - Summit Strike (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Ghost Recon 2 : Summit Strike</name>
		<desc>Ghost Recon 2: Summit Strike on Xbox is a first-person tactical shooter. With the support of the UN, take command of the Ghosts to track a Pakistani warlord across Kazakhstan and prevent a national disaster. Experience the adrenaline and risk of leading the elite. Experience a new single-player campaign featuring eleven missions, fifteen new weapons, four new vehicles and new combat gear.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 - Summit Strike (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 - Summit Strike (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 2 - Summit Strike (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Storm Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15371">
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Critical Hour (USA) (En,Fr).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Rainbow Six : Critical Hour</name>
		<desc>Critical Hour is the fourth Rainbow Six game to appear on the consoles. You play as Ding Chavez, leading a small commando team on black-ops missions. The main single player revisits seven of the most popular missions from the original Rainbow Six and Rogue Spear game, recreated with modern technology. The game returns to the roots of the franchise with tactical gameplay and "one-shot kills".



There is a split-screen mode available and full online multiplayer  featuring modes like Practice Mission, Terrorist Hunt, Team Survival, Total Conquest, Retrieval, Team Sharpshooter, Free-for-All Survival (new), Free-for-All Sharpshooter (New) and Assassin (new). Up to 16 players can compete over Xbox Live.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Critical Hour (USA) (En,Fr).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Critical Hour (USA) (En,Fr).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Critical Hour (USA) (En,Fr).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six</family>
		<players>16</players>
		<lang>en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14633">
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Chaos Theory (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Splinter Cell Chaos Theory</name>
		<desc>Splinter Cell Chaos Theory on Xbox is an infiltration game in which you once again play as Sam Fisher. From Panama to Korea via the USA, the goal remains more or less the same, to get as close as possible to your target thanks to a wide range of moves. Hang from the ceiling and then suspend yourself above a track riddled with motion-detecting lasers. Or would you rather slip into this narrow duct?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Chaos Theory (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Chaos Theory (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Chaos Theory (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>Splinter Cell</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14636">
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Double Agent (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Splinter Cell Double Agent</name>
		<desc>Splinter Cell Double Agent is an infiltration game for Xbox. You play as Sam Fisher again, this time as a double agent. In the game, his morals and loyalty to his employers and his country are paramount. He must do everything to protect his cover, which is what keeps him on the edge of his seat throughout the title. It is up to you to make the right choices, which will directly influence the scenario.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Double Agent (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Double Agent (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Double Agent (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<family>Splinter Cell</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>de,en,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14874">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<desc>Drop into the ultimate challenge. In the next chapter in the Tony Hawk series, pros challenge you to make your mark in huge free-roaming levels, taking on 190 progressively harder goals with no time limits to hold you back. Decide when you're ready to take on your Pro Challenge and move into the pro ranks, where it's a whole new game. Build your skills, perform all-new tricks, play up to eight players online, and show that you've got what it takes to go Pro.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15418">
		<path>./TransWorld Snowboarding (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Transworld Snowboarding</name>
		<desc>While it's true that everything that goes up must come down, it's the ones who come down in style that count. That's what you'll be doing in TransWorld Snowboarding -- barrelling down the packed powder slopes at breakneck speeds while pulling off insane tricks, jibs and grinds on the quarter- and half-pipes, snow kickers and ramps. This is no bunny trail; you'll have to look out for steep cliffs, downed trees, ice blocks, and all manner of other mountain hazards. Choose from ten snowboarder pros and outfit them in the latest gear from real manufacturers such as Oakley and Volcomhit. Then hit the powder in real locations all over the world. Developer Housemarque has harnessed the power of the Xbox's graphics hardware to produce an extreme snowboarding event that's poised to give SSX a run for its money.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TransWorld Snowboarding (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TransWorld Snowboarding (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TransWorld Snowboarding (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Housemarque</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skiing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15005">
		<path>./TransWorld Surf (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Transworld Surf</name>
		<desc>TransWorld Surf lets you pull off all the massive airs and blazing tailslides of professional surfers, including Taj Burrow, Andy Irons, and Shane Dorian. This is your chance to drop into more than 20 of the world's most challenging breaks in locations such as Todos Santos, Hossegor, and Tavarua. Conquer the waves with a friend, hitch a ride with the Reef Girls, watch out for the hungry sharks, and remember to save your best moves for photographers who just may put you on the in-game cover of TransWorld Surf.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TransWorld Surf (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/TransWorld Surf (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TransWorld Surf (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Angel Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14685">
		<path>./True Crime - New York City (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>True Crime : New York City</name>
		<desc>True Crime: New York City on Xbox puts you in the shoes of Marcus Reed in the middle of the urban jungle. As an ex-voyote turned cop, it's up to you to carry out your missions as you see fit: dirty or clean. Find your mentor's killer by carrying out missions for one side or the other. Arrests, interrogations, chases, extortion... Anything is possible when the law is on your side.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/True Crime - New York City (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/True Crime - New York City (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/True Crime - New York City (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Luxoflux</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14800">
		<path>./True Crime - Streets of LA (USA, Asia).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>True Crime : Streets of LA</name>
		<desc>As Nick Kang, your brutal reputation and lethal skills have landed you a nasty job: heading up an undercover task force to stop the Chinese and Russian gangs from terrorizing Los Angeles. Drive, fight, and blast your way through a massive array of unpredictable missions, using stealth techniques, martial arts moves, and an ask-questions-later arsenal. True Crime features a branching storyline that gives you the freedom to complete missions as you choose and face the consequences later. The hardcore streets of L.A. have met their match.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/True Crime - Streets of LA (USA, Asia).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/True Crime - Streets of LA (USA, Asia).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/True Crime - Streets of LA (USA, Asia).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20031103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Luxoflux</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14655">
		<path>./Turok - Evolution (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Turok Evolution</name>
		<desc>Turok Evolution is a FPS for Xbox. Join the war raging in the Forgotten Lands against Lord Tyrannus and his army of reptiles. The game features an impressive arsenal of 15 devastating weapons for an adventure through the jungle, military camps, rivers and fortresses. The player also experiences aerial battles on the back of dinosaurs!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Turok - Evolution (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Turok - Evolution (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turok - Evolution (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Turok</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15281">
		<path>./AirForce Delta Storm (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>AirForce Delta Storm</name>
		<desc>Strap into your cockpit and blast through the gut-wrenching world of flight combat. Your adrenaline pumps as machinegun fire pelts off your tail, you execute backbreaking barrel rolls and experience dog-fighting action.

Take your pick of over 70 planes, including military fighters rendered from actual aircraft. With a full range of extreme missions to numb your Xbox to the sky!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AirForce Delta Storm (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/AirForce Delta Storm (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AirForce Delta Storm (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Vehicle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15065">
		<path>./Barbie Horse Adventures - Wild Horse Rescue (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Barbie Horse Adventures : Wild Horse Rescue</name>
		<desc>Ride through five stunning areas, jump over fallen trees, cross rickety bridges, and avoid other potential hazards throughout their quest. Guide Barbie and her horse over thin cliff edges and logs in rivers, leading Barbie to dismount her horse and explore the trails on foot. You can even help Barbie climb ledges and swing hand over hand along low branches.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Barbie Horse Adventures - Wild Horse Rescue (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Barbie Horse Adventures - Wild Horse Rescue (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Barbie Horse Adventures - Wild Horse Rescue (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>Blitz Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Barbie</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15459">
		<path>./Bicycle Casino Includes - Texas Hold'em (USA, Europe).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Bicycle Casino</name>
		<desc>All In ! No Limit ! Texas Hold'em is sweeping the world, and it's now available online via Xbox Live for you to ante up and get in on the action. Bicycle Casino will keep everyone from the novice to the shark on the edge of their seats with fast-paced action and over 500 different game variations to choose from. So pull up your favorite chair and get in on the game today !</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bicycle Casino Includes - Texas Hold'em (USA, Europe).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bicycle Casino Includes - Texas Hold'em (USA, Europe).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bicycle Casino Includes - Texas Hold'em (USA, Europe).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20050707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoo Digital Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Leaping Lizard Games</publisher>
		<genre>Playing cards</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14738">
		<path>./Black (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Black</name>
		<desc>Join the world's most brutal and enigmatic strike force. The BLACK tactical squad operates under the cloak of complete anonymity and deniability to protect the U.S. from threats foreign and domestic. It answers to no one, allowing it to carry out covert operations around the globe. From manipulating politicians to controlling intelligence networks and militaries, BLACK operatives are trained at the highest level in psychological warfare, espionage, and lethal combat. Go deep into the world of clandestine warfare as you use any means necessary to get the job done.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Black (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Black (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Black (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="137559">
		<path>./Broken Sword - The Sleeping Dragon (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Broken Sword : The Sleeping Dragon</name>
		<desc>The Sleeping Dragon moves away from the 2D point-and-click concept from the earlier games and features a full 3D world, with a camera that does not rotate, but uses fixed cinematic perspectives. The player alternately controls George or Nico. Next to typical adventure gameplay such as exploration, conversations, and searching and combining items, there are also a few action sequences. The characters can duck, sneak, hang from ledges and move crates to reach higher areas. The locations visited throughout the game include The Congo, Paris, England, Czech Republic and Egypt.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Broken Sword - The Sleeping Dragon (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Broken Sword - The Sleeping Dragon (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Broken Sword - The Sleeping Dragon (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20031204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revolution Software</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14729">
		<path>./Dead or Alive Ultimate (USA, Japan) (En,Ja).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Dead Or Alive : Ultimate</name>
		<desc>Dead or Alive Ultimate combines the original Dead or Alive with a redesigned Dead or Alive 2 and takes the series online for the first time. Both games can be played on Xbox Live, which enables you to test your fighting skills against gamers from around the world. The new Dead or Alive 2 Ultimate features episodes from the characters' pasts that reveal new details surrounding some of the most popular characters.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead or Alive Ultimate (USA, Japan) (En,Ja).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead or Alive Ultimate (USA, Japan) (En,Ja).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead or Alive Ultimate (USA, Japan) (En,Ja).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<family>Dead or Alive</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<md5>264c8858f2b390270d67f3bb9ea4184c</md5>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14630">
		<path>./Doom 3 (USA, Asia) (Limited Collector's Edition).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Doom 3</name>
		<desc>The third game of the DOOM series (now in full 3D) takes gamers through the depths of Hell, where technology and demons meet. But this time round, the game is more focused on horror elements than previous games in series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Doom 3 (USA, Asia) (Limited Collector's Edition).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Doom 3 (USA, Asia) (Limited Collector's Edition).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Doom 3 (USA, Asia) (Limited Collector's Edition).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Doom</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14611">
		<path>./Fable - The Lost Chapters (USA) (En,Es).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Fable : The Lost Chapters</name>
		<desc>The Lost Chapters features all the content found in the original Fable, as well as additional new content such as new monsters, weapons, alignment based spells, items, armour, towns, buildings, and expressions, as well as the ability to give children objects. The story receives further augmentation in the form of nine new areas and sixteen additional quests. Characters such as Briar Rose and Scythe, who played only minor roles in the original game, are now given more importance and are included in certain main and side quests. Other character-based augmentations include the voice of the antagonist, Jack of Blades, sounding deeper, harsher and more demonic, and the ability to uncover (and resolve) the murder mystery of Lady Grey's sister.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fable - The Lost Chapters (USA) (En,Es).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fable - The Lost Chapters (USA) (En,Es).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fable - The Lost Chapters (USA) (En,Es).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Lionhead</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,es</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="15498">
		<path>./Maximum Chase (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Maximum Chase</name>
		<desc>In this forever pursuit of a game, you play as a cop who has just got off duty. In a movie sequence you have a girl that gets in your car fleeing from a mob of mysterious people shooting, while you just got off duty. Little to know is this may be the destruction of Los Angeles.



This game has a storyline where you must run from all kinds of obstacles, cars, and people, through the entire game. Choose from 5 different cars, and shoot arcade style from a car while a girl drives.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Maximum Chase (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Maximum Chase (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Maximum Chase (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20031106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14860" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Project Gotham Racing (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Project Gotham Racing</name>
		<desc>Project Gotham Racing est un jeu de courses sur Xbox qui vous propose 25 voitures dont la Ferrari F50, la Porsche Boxster S, la Corvette Z06 et l'Aston Martin Vanquish. Roulez sur plus de 200 circuits de New York à Tokyo en passant par Londres et San Francisco. Amassez les points Kudos en faisant preuve de vitesse, de style et d'habileté pour débloquer des bonus. Project Gotham Racing est jouable à 4 en écran séparé.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Project Gotham Racing (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Project Gotham Racing (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Project Gotham Racing (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<genreid>1537</genreid>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Starfighter Special Edition (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars Starfighter: Special Edition</name>
		<desc>The story begins by showing one of the four main characters, Rhys Dallows, piloting an N-1 Naboo Starfighter. He manages to blast one droid starfighter out of the sky, but is subsequently shot by a second one. It is then revealed Rhys was just dreaming, as he is awakened by Essara Till, who trains him in basic maneuvering and combat. The two are then relegated to defending the Queen of Naboo as they meet with Trade Federation officials. The meeting is revealed to be a trap, as Rhys and Essara are then forced to defend the royal starship until it can escape. Essara is killed by an unidentified ship, while Rhys survives and is later rescued by the Toydarian Reti.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Starfighter Special Edition (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Starfighter Special Edition (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Starfighter Special Edition (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20011126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Secret Level Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="14614" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Halo 2 (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko).iso</path>
		<name>Halo 2</name>
		<desc>Halo 2 is the sequel to the highly successful and critically acclaimed Halo®: Combat Evolved. In Halo 2, the saga continues as Master Chief?a genetically enhanced super-soldier?is the only thing standing between the relentless Covenant and the destruction of all humankind.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Halo 2 (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Halo 2 (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halo 2 (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Zh,Ko).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bungie</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Game Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action</genre>
		<players>2-16</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>de,en,jp,es,fr,it</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<genreid>259</genreid>
	</game>
	<game id="14645">
		<path>./Shenmue II (USA).xiso.iso</path>
		<name>Shenmue II</name>
		<desc>Yu Suzuki's cinematic masterpiece returns with more spellbinding adventure and an even more immersive world. The epic continues as Ryo Hazuki arrives in Hong Kong on his quest to avenge his father's murder by the warlord Lan Di and unravel the mystery of the Phoenix mirror. Set in Hong Kong, Kowloon, and Guilin, you'll travel through breathtaking scenery, rich with mountainous wilderness, traditional Taoist temples, and stunning tropical landscapes. As you move through massive, highly-detailed 3D worlds, you'll interact with almost every facet of your environment as well as a whole new cast of characters.



Originally released on Dreamcast in Europe and Japan, this Xbox edition marks the sequel's debut in the US and includes the Shenmue Movie chronicling the first episode in the series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shenmue II (USA).xiso.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shenmue II (USA).xiso.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shenmue II (USA).xiso.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19691231T200000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>AM2</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bruce Lee - Quest of the Dragon.iso</path>
		<name>Bruce Lee: Quest of the Dragon</name>
		<desc>Bruce Lee: Quest of the Dragon is a beat 'em up video game featuring martial artist Bruce Lee. It was developed by Ronin Entertainment and published by Universal Interactive, and was released in Europe and the United States for the Xbox in 2002 to a negative critical reception.

You are Bruce Lee, legendary martial arts master. Your father has been kidnapped, your monastery desecrated, and the mystical Golden Relic - keeper of the ancient martial arts secrets - has been stolen. Investigate the mysterious Black Lotus crime organization and the beautiful and deadly Dragon Lady. Use your mastery of Jeet Kune Do to punch, kick, block and combo as you fight hordes of thugs and crime bosses. In this compelling blend of epic adventure and intense fighting action you finally get the chance to be Bruce Lee.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bruce Lee - Quest of the Dragon.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bruce Lee - Quest of the Dragon.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bruce Lee - Quest of the Dragon.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20020701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ronin Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fuzion Frenzy.iso</path>
		<name>Fuzion Frenzy</name>
		<desc>Fuzion Frenzy is a launch title for the Microsoft Xbox. At its core, Fuzion Frenzy is a four-player party game featuring 45 different mini-games (not including the titular Fuzion Frenzy). A demo of the game was included with some other launch titles in the US, including Halo, Munch's Oddysee, the first Project Gotham Racing game and Amped. The title was among the first to be released as a part of the Xbox Originals program.



A sequel was later released for the Xbox 360, entitled Fuzion Frenzy 2.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fuzion Frenzy.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fuzion Frenzy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fuzion Frenzy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<md5>77f79c168f2d859aef09936ff708a15a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkwatch.iso</path>
		<name>Darkwatch</name>
		<desc>The game's story (narrated by Peter Jason) follows the exploits of Jericho Cross, an outlaw-turned-vampire, and his employment in an ancient vampire-hunting order known as the Darkwatch (hence the game's title). After unwittingly releasing the Darkwatch's greatest enemy, a vampire lord named Lazarus Malkoth, Jericho is conscripted into the Darkwatch as an elite operative. Jericho, however, is slowly turning into a vampire himself, after being bitten by Lazarus. The game outlines either Jericho's struggle for humanity or his descent into darkness, depending on the player's actions. The game begins in Arizona Territory in 1876 with Jericho attempting to rob a Darkwatch train that is transporting the captured Lazarus Malkoth to the Darkwatch Citadel, a frequently mentioned and often visited location in the game, and in doing so releases Lazarus into the West. In a seeming bit of mercy, Lazarus bites Jericho and gives him the curse of the vampire, causing him to slowly turn into one. The game continues with the introduction of Cassidy as well as the appearance of Shadow, Jericho's undead horse. As the game progresses, Jericho finally makes his way to the Darkwatch Citadel, where he meets General Clay Cartwright, the current leader of the order. Cartwright puts him through Torture Maze, the Darkwatch initiation exercise which was designed as a test for Darkwatch Regulators, but Jericho gets a special version specially designed by Cartwright to kill him.[7] When Jericho passes the test anyway, he begins to do missions for the Darkwatch. Missions include tasks ranging from fixing some of the damage he has caused to acquiring Darkwatch equipment, such as the Darklight Prism, a stone that allows vampires within its vicinity to use their powers and walk in sunlight.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Darkwatch.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Darkwatch.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Darkwatch.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Moon Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>16</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
